<root><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take the coffee  | . Pour it to the mug  | . Put ice cream and the syrup to the mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the coffee. Pour it to the mug. Put ice cream and the syrup to the mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Take all cups, mugs, spoons, and forks  | and place in sink  | . Toggle sink  | on . Arrange all other small items on counter  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take all cups, mugs, spoons, and forks and place in sink. Toggle sink on. Arrange all other small items on counter</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Put the pot in the sink  | and then fill it up with water  | . Put the pot on the stove  | and then turn on the stove  | . Get the ramen  | and put it in pot  | when the water in the pot is boiling  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the pot in the sink and then fill it up with water. Put the pot on the stove and then turn on the stove. Get the ramen and put it in pot when the water in the pot is boiling. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Grab the ramen  | and add water  | . Place it in the microwave  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grab the ramen and add water. Place it in the microwave.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Put the movie in the Xbox  | and turn the television input to Xbox  | . Put bag of chips on table  | . Put pillows on couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the movie in the Xbox and turn the television input to Xbox. Put bag of chips on table. Put pillows on couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put the xbox controller and remote on the desk  | . Give me the bag of chips  | . Put the cd's on the shelf .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the xbox controller and remote on the desk. Give me the bag of chips. Put the cd's on the shelf</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Get all the plates, cups, and spoons on the counters  | and put them in the sink  | . Take the mug from the microwave  | and pour its contents into the sink  | and then place it in the sink  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get all the plates, cups, and spoons on the counters and put them in the sink. Take the mug from the microwave and pour its contents into the sink and then place it in the sink.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take  | coffee pot pour into the mug  | . Take  | spoon from counter scoop the ice cream  | . Put ice cream to the mug  | . Pour syrup to the mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take coffee pot pour into the mug. Take spoon from counter scoop the ice cream. Put ice cream to the mug. Pour syrup to the mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Place the Xbox and Xbox controller  | underneath the television console . Place  | all of the couches on one side of the wall, preferably facing the television  | . Place all of the beer and bags of chips on the white counter  | . Place the garbage bin near the white counter  | . Place the trash bag inside the garbage bin  | . Turn on the television  | to channel  | 3 and increase the volume  | to 50 . Place the CD's on a shelf  | . Place  | the coke can on the counter along with the beer and chips  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place the Xbox and Xbox controller underneath the television console. Place all of the couches on one side of the wall, preferably facing the television. Place all of the beer and bags of chips on the white counter. Place the garbage bin near the white counter. Place the trash bag inside the garbage bin. Turn on the television to channel 3 and increase the volume to 50. Place the CD's on a shelf. Place the coke can on the counter along with the beer and chips. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Put the pot in the sink, fill it up and boil the water on the stove  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the pot in the sink, fill it up and boil the water on the stove.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put the game in the  xbox  | . Turn the television input to Xbox  | . Put bag of chips and coke on table  | . Move couch in front of television  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the game in the  xbox. Turn the television input to Xbox. Put bag of chips and coke on table. Move couch in front of television.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Turn off the tv  | . Put snacks and books on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off the tv. Put snacks and books on the table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put pillows on couch  | . Put beer and chips in trash  | can .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put pillows on couch. Put beer and chips in trash can.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn music  | on . Put beer and chips on table  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn music on. Put beer and chips on table. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Grab the game cd  | . Place the cd in the xobx  | . Prepare us food  | and bring the coke  | . Take the pillow from the shelf  | and put it to the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grab the game cd. Place the cd in the xobx. Prepare us food and bring the coke. Take the pillow from the shelf and put it to the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put the pillows on the couch  | and turn the chairs towards the TV  | . Open the bag of chips  | and pour it onto the plate  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the pillows on the couch and turn the chairs towards the TV. Open the bag of chips and pour it onto the plate.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Open refrigerator  | . Grab food and drink  | . Grab cups and plates  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Open refrigerator. Grab food and drink. Grab cups and plates. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Put all the cds on the table in front of the couch  | . Pour some chips  | . Put soda on the table  | . Put the pillows on the couch  | turn the tv  | on and put the xbox controller on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all the cds on the table in front of the couch. Pour some chips. Put soda on the table. Put the pillows on the couch turn the tv on and put the xbox controller on the table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Place the TV remote on the center table  | . Bring the xBox and Xbox controllers  | in front of the television . Plug in the Xbox to the television  | and activate all game controllers  | . Place the controllers on the center table  | . Place the bowl of food, beer, and coke on the center table  | . Fix the pillows on the couch  | . Put the garbage bag inside the garbage bin and place the bin near the two seater couch  Put the garbage bag inside the garbage bin and place the bin near the two seater  | couch .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place the TV remote on the center table. Bring the xBox and Xbox controllers in front of the television. Plug in the Xbox to the television and activate all game controllers. Place the controllers on the center table. Place the bowl of food, beer, and coke on the center table. Fix the pillows on the couch. Put the garbage bag inside the garbage bin and place the bin near the two seater couch. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn music  | on . Dispose of garbage bag . Put pillow on couch  | . Put bowl and beer and coke on table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn music on. Dispose of garbage bag. Put pillow on couch. Put bowl and beer and coke on table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Fill pot with water  | . Put pot on stove  | . Turn stove  | on .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill pot with water. Put pot on stove. Turn stove on.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Open the fridge  | and get the boiled egg  | and put it on plate  | 2 . Open the fridge  | and get the canada  | dry and put it next to plate  | 2 .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Open the fridge and get the boiled egg and put it on plate 2. Open the fridge and get the canada dry and put it next to plate 2.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Grab a cup,  | and fill the cup with milk  | .  Next grab a bowl .  Fill the bowl with cereal  | .  Slowly add milk to the same bowl  | . Put the cup and bowl next to each other, along with a spoon  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grab a cup, and fill the cup with milk.  Next grab a bowl.  Fill the bowl with cereal.  Slowly add milk to the same bowl. Put the cup and bowl next to each other, along with a spoon.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Open freezer door  | and grab ice cream  | . Grab spoon  | and use it  | to put ice cream in coffee mug  | . Grab chocolate syrup bottle  | and add to coffee  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Open freezer door and grab ice cream. Grab spoon and use it to put ice cream in coffee mug. Grab chocolate syrup bottle and add to coffee.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>123 .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : 123</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Grab plates and cups  | and bring  | to sink  | . Put ice cream in freezer  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grab plates and cups and bring to sink. Put ice cream in freezer.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Turn stove  | on . Grab  | pot  | and bring  | to sink  | . Fill pot with water  | . Put pot on stove  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn stove on. Grab pot and bring to sink. Fill pot with water. Put pot on stove.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Make coffee  | .  Take a bowl, ice cream scoop,  | and ice cream .  Use  | the ice cream scoop  | to add ice cream to the bowl  | twice .  Slowly pour the finished coffee into the bowl  | .  Get the syrup  | and squirt two tablespoons on top  | .  serve with a spoon  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Make coffee.  Take a bowl, ice cream scoop, and ice cream.  Use the ice cream scoop to add ice cream to the bowl twice.  Slowly pour the finished coffee into the bowl.  Get the syrup and squirt two tablespoons on top.  serve with a spoon</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Bring pot to sink and fill with water  | . Put pot on stove  | . Turn on stove  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Bring pot to sink and fill with water. Put pot on stove. Turn on stove.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put the xbox in front of the TV  | and hook up the wires  | and plug it into an outlet  | . Plug the controller into the xbox  | and put it on the table in front of the couch  | . Change the input  | of the TV to display the xbox  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the xbox in front of the TV and hook up the wires and plug it into an outlet. Plug the controller into the xbox and put it on the table in front of the couch. Change the input of the TV to display the xbox.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Bring pot to sink  | . Fill pot with water  | . Put pot on stove  | . Turn stove  | on .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Bring pot to sink. Fill pot with water. Put pot on stove. Turn stove on.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Grasp the vanilla syrup bottle  | . Open the fridge door  | and place the bottle inside the fridge  | . Close the fridge door  | . Carry Glass1, long cup1, Mug, Long Cup2, pot, and spoon near the sink . Empty the contents of the mug into the sink  | and clean the sink with the running water  | . Place the instant ramen, ramen,  | and salt bottle into their designated pantries  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grasp the vanilla syrup bottle. Open the fridge door and place the bottle inside the fridge. Close the fridge door. Carry Glass1, long cup1, Mug, Long Cup2, pot, and spoon near the sink. Empty the contents of the mug into the sink and clean the sink with the running water. Place the instant ramen, ramen, and salt bottle into their designated pantries. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Bring plates and cups to sink  | . Put ice cream in refrigerator  | . Put ramen in cabinet  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Bring plates and cups to sink. Put ice cream in refrigerator. Put ramen in cabinet.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn music  | on . Put chips coke and beer on table  | . Put pillows on couch  | . Put Xbox and controller on TV  | stand .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn music on. Put chips coke and beer on table. Put pillows on couch. Put Xbox and controller on TV stand.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Put the pot in the sink  | and fill it up three quarters of the way with water  | . Bring the pot onto the stove  | and turn the stove  | on . When the water is boiling,  | turn the stove  | off .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the pot in the sink and fill it up three quarters of the way with water. Bring the pot onto the stove and turn the stove on. When the water is boiling, turn the stove off.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Put movie in Xbox  | . Turn television on to Xbox input  | . Put chips on table  | . Arrange pillows on couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put movie in Xbox. Turn television on to Xbox input. Put chips on table. Arrange pillows on couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Get a pot  | and fill it with water from the tap  | .  Put the pot on the stove  | and turn the heat of the appropriate burner  | on "medium ."  Get the package of ramen and open it  | .  Add the ramen to the water  | .  After a few minutes pour the contents of the pot into a bowl . Serve with a fork  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get a pot and fill it with water from the tap.  Put the pot on the stove and turn the heat of the appropriate burner on "medium."  Get the package of ramen and open it.  Add the ramen to the water.  After a few minutes pour the contents of the pot into a bowl. Serve with a fork.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>test  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : test</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Grab cup and glass  | and fill with sink water  | . Open refrigerator  | and grab food  | . Put food on plate  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grab cup and glass and fill with sink water. Open refrigerator and grab food. Put food on plate.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Put all the school books on the table  | . Turn off the tv  | and pour some chips and drinks  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all the school books on the table. Turn off the tv and pour some chips and drinks</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Grab CD  | . Turn music  | on . Put chips and bowl on table  | . Arrange pillow on couch  | . Dispose garbage bag  | . Arrange books on table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grab CD. Turn music on. Put chips and bowl on table. Arrange pillow on couch. Dispose garbage bag. Arrange books on table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn on TV  | . Bring us coke and the beer  | . Place the pillows on the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on TV. Bring us coke and the beer. Place the pillows on the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Fill up the bowl with chips  | and put it on the table  | . If the bag of chips is empty throw away the bag in the garbage bag |  If the bag of chips is empty throw away the bag in the garbage bag . Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin |  Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill up the bowl with chips and put it on the table. If the bag of chips is empty throw away the bag in the garbage bag. Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Grab CD  | . Turn music  | on . Arrange chips on table  | . Arrange couches in organized position  | . Dispose garbage bag  | . Arrange books on table  | . Arrange pillows on couch  | . Throw away beer and coke  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grab CD. Turn music on. Arrange chips on table. Arrange couches in organized position. Dispose garbage bag. Arrange books on table. Arrange pillows on couch. Throw away beer and coke.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Place the pillows on the couch  | . Put the beer bottle in the trash bin  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place the pillows on the couch. Put the beer bottle in the trash bin.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jsb346@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Arrange books on table  | . Turn off television  | . Arrange chips on table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Arrange books on table. Turn off television. Arrange chips on table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Grasp the spoon, fork, mug, and glass  | and bring to the sink  | . Empty the contents of the glass  | and mug into the sink  | and rinse the dishes  | . Clean the sink with the running water . Grab the Vanilla Syrup Bottle and Chocolate  | Syrup Bottle, and open the fridge door  | . Place the bottles inside the fridge  | and close the fridge door  | . Place the instant ramen  | to its designated pantry  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grasp the spoon, fork, mug, and glass and bring to the sink. Empty the contents of the glass and mug into the sink and rinse the dishes. Clean the sink with the running water. Grab the Vanilla Syrup Bottle and Chocolate Syrup Bottle, and open the fridge door. Place the bottles inside the fridge and close the fridge door. Place the instant ramen to its designated pantry. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Open the cup of instant ramen  | halfway and fill it up with water from the sink  | . Flatten the cover  | and put the instant ramen into the microwave  | and cook it  | for the specified time on the cup  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Open the cup of instant ramen halfway and fill it up with water from the sink. Flatten the cover and put the instant ramen into the microwave and cook it for the specified time on the cup.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>put coffee in cup open the freezer and put ice cream in it then add  | chocolate syrup .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : put coffee in cup open the freezer and put ice cream in it then add chocolate syrup.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Put  | all the school books on the table turn off the tv  | and get chips and soda on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all the school books on the table turn off the tv and get chips and soda on the table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put the game cd on xbox  | . Bring us chips  | . Put the left pillow to right couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the game cd on xbox. Bring us chips. Put the left pillow to right couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Get water in the pot from the sink then boil the water on the stove .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get water in the pot from the sink then boil the water on the stove</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Collect the plates, utensils, and cups  | and put them in the sink  | . Take the mug from the microwave  | and empty its contents into the sink  | and put it in the sink  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Collect the plates, utensils, and cups and put them in the sink. Take the mug from the microwave and empty its contents into the sink and put it in the sink.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>place  | all the school books on the table turn off the tv  | and put chips and soda on the table
  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : place all the school books on the table turn off the tv and put chips and soda on the table
</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put the empty cup and the dish to the sink  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the empty cup and the dish to the sink. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>If anything is disposable and used, put it in the trash bag  | .  If it is not disposable and on the floor, put it on the table nearest any items associated with it   If it is not disposable and on the floor, put it on the table nearest any items associated with it |   If it is not disposable and on the floor, put it on the table nearest any items associated with it .  If a not disposable item contains only disposable objects, dump them into the trash bag,  | and treat the object  | like it was on the floor  | .  Remove the trash bag from the scenario  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : If anything is disposable and used, put it in the trash bag.  If it is not disposable and on the floor, put it on the table nearest any items associated with it.  If a not disposable item contains only disposable objects, dump them into the trash bag, and treat the object like it was on the floor.  Remove the trash bag from the scenario</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put the cd's next to the tv,  | trash any open food  | and place all the controllers and remotes on the table  | and pick up the pillows  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the cd's next to the tv, trash any open food and place all the controllers and remotes on the table and pick up the pillows.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Put the pillows on the couch and the books on the table in front  | of the couch . Turn off the TV  | . Bring the other chairs around the table in front of the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the pillows on the couch and the books on the table in front of the couch. Turn off the TV. Bring the other chairs around the table in front of the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on the music  | . Bring us chips and coke  | . Bring us the controller  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the music. Bring us chips and coke. Bring us the controller.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Put all the cd's  | on the table get chips and soda  | and make sure the pillows are on the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all the cd's on the table get chips and soda and make sure the pillows are on the couch</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take coffee from the container pour it into mug  | . Scoop the ice-cream  | and pour syrup  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take coffee from the container pour it into mug. Scoop the ice-cream and pour syrup</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Place both CD's and both books (brown and Guiness) on top of the shelf in the corner of the room . Bring bag of chips and place on the center coffee table . Place all couches on the side of one wall  | . Put the garbage bag inside the bin  | and place near the wall and near the counter  | . Put one of the CD's  | into the Xbox console and place the Xbox console near the television and turn on the power into the Xbox console and place  | the Xbox console near the television and turn on the power  | . Music can play  | from there .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place both CD's and both books (brown and Guiness) on top of the shelf in the corner of the room. Bring bag of chips and place on the center coffee table. Place all couches on the side of one wall. Put the garbage bag inside the bin and place near the wall and near the counter. Put one of the CD's into the Xbox console and place the Xbox console near the television and turn on the power. Music can play from there. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put all cds and games next to the xbox  | . Make sure the xbox is next to the tv  | . Put the controllers and remotes on the table  | . Pick of the pillows  | . And throw out any garbage  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all cds and games next to the xbox. Make sure the xbox is next to the tv. Put the controllers and remotes on the table. Pick of the pillows. And throw out any garbage.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Bring the pot to the sink  | and fill it up with water  | . Bring the pot to the stove  | and turn on the stove  | . Turn off the stove  | when the water in the pot is boiling  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Bring the pot to the sink and fill it up with water. Bring the pot to the stove and turn on the stove. Turn off the stove when the water in the pot is boiling.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put the xbox and the xbox  | controllet on the shelf . Put the bag of chips  | to trash bin  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the xbox and the xbox controllet on the shelf. Put the bag of chips to trash bin.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Make some coffee  | . Make an egg on the stove  | and then bring it  | to me .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Make some coffee. Make an egg on the stove and then bring it to me.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put cs to game box  | . Bring is bag of chips and the coke . Put pillows on the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put cs to game box. Bring is bag of chips and the coke. Put pillows on the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on the TV  | and turn the volume to the max  | . Put the garbage bag into the garbage can |  Put the garbage bag into the garbage can .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the TV and turn the volume to the max. Put the garbage bag into the garbage can.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Make some coffee  | . Cook some eggs on the stove  | and then bring it  | to me .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Make some coffee. Cook some eggs on the stove and then bring it to me</span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn on the TV and the XBOX  | . Make  | sure they are connected  | . Open the disk tray of the XBOX  | and insert the DVD  | after removing it from its  | case . Close the tray  | . Find  | and open the bag of chips  | . Find a large bowl,  | and pour chips into it  | until it is filled  | . Put all drinks in the room with the bowl of chips on the coffee table  | . Take the pillows and divide them evenly among the chairs  | .  Clean anything trash  | unless it's needed  | above .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the TV and the XBOX. Make sure they are connected. Open the disk tray of the XBOX and insert the DVD after removing it from its case. Close the tray. Find and open the bag of chips. Find a large bowl, and pour chips into it until it is filled. Put all drinks in the room with the bowl of chips on the coffee table. Take the pillows and divide them evenly among the chairs.  Clean anything trash unless it's needed above.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put the used dishes and cups in the sink  | and place all the items neatly on the counter and place all the items neatly on the counter  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the used dishes and cups in the sink and place all the items neatly on the counter</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Place both books on the center table  | . Hold the trash bag in one hand  | and place the plate inside the bag  | . Place the empty coke can, beer, and bag of chips into the trash  | bag . Arrange the couches  | in the correct locations in the living room  | . Pick up Guiness book from the floor and place on desk  | . turn off the lamp  | . Place the three pillows on the couches  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place both books on the center table. Hold the trash bag in one hand and place the plate inside the bag. Place the empty coke can, beer, and bag of chips into the trash bag. Arrange the couches in the correct locations in the living room. Pick up Guiness book from the floor and place on desk. turn off the lamp. Place the three pillows on the couches. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Get ramen  | . Boil water on the stove  | and pour ramen to boiled water  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get ramen. Boil water on the stove and pour ramen to boiled water.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Fill the pot with water in the sink the boil it on the stove  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the pot with water in the sink the boil it on the stove.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put the empty bag of chips  | to trash bin  | . Put the pillows on the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the empty bag of chips to trash bin. Put the pillows on the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Put the pillows on the couch  | . Turn on the TV  | and change it to a channel with a movie  | . Take beer  | and put it on the table in front of the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the pillows on the couch. Turn on the TV and change it to a channel with a movie. Take beer and put it on the table in front of the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Put the pillows on the couch,  | play some music on the xbox through the tv  | . Clean the floor up . Put some food on the table  | . Make sure all the books are on the shelf  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the pillows on the couch, play some music on the xbox through the tv. Clean the floor up. Put some food on the table. Make sure all the books are on the shelf</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Place pot on the stove  | and turn the stove  | on . Go and get the instant ramen  | . Wait for the water in the pot  | to boil Open the ramen packet  | and dump contents into boiling water  | . Read the instructions  | and prepare  | accordingly . Empty contents of pot onto the plate . Put the chocolate syrup into the fridge  | . Remove mug  | and close the microwave door  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place pot on the stove and turn the stove on. Go and get the instant ramen. Wait for the water in the pot to boil Open the ramen packet and dump contents into boiling water. Read the instructions and prepare accordingly. Empty contents of pot onto the plate. Put the chocolate syrup into the fridge. Remove mug and close the microwave door. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>mst95@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Make some coffee  | . Make some eggs on the stove  | and then put them on a plate  | and serve the eggs and coffee  | to me .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Make some coffee. Make some eggs on the stove and then put them on a plate and serve the eggs and coffee to me</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Get  | the water pour into bowl  | . Place bowl on the stove . Boil water  | . Pour ramen into bowl  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the water pour into bowl. Place bowl on the stove. Boil water. Pour ramen into bowl.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Get  | the water pour into bowl  | . Place the bowl on the stove  | . Boil water  | . Pour ramen ino the bowl .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the water pour into bowl. Place the bowl on the stove. Boil water. Pour ramen ino the bowl.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Get  | the water pour into bowl  | . Place the bowl on the stove  | . Boil water  | . Pour ramen ino the bowl .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the water pour into bowl. Place the bowl on the stove. Boil water. Pour ramen ino the bowl.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Place the pillows on the couch  | . Put the trash bag in the trash bin |  Put the trash bag in the trash bin . Put the couches in their correct locations  | . Turn on the television  | and put  | to channel  | 20 and play the movie  | . Arrange the food on the center table  | . Turn of the lights  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place the pillows on the couch. Put the trash bag in the trash bin. Put the couches in their correct locations. Turn on the television and put to channel 20 and play the movie. Arrange the food on the center table. Turn of the lights. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Take the pot to the stove  | and fill it up half way with water  | . Put the pot on the stove  | and turn the stove  | on . Open the cup of ramen  | and wait for the water to boil  | . When the water is boiling,  | pour the cup of ramen's contents into the pot  | . Turn the stove  | off when it is done  | cooking  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the pot to the stove and fill it up half way with water. Put the pot on the stove and turn the stove on. Open the cup of ramen and wait for the water to boil. When the water is boiling, pour the cup of ramen's contents into the pot. Turn the stove off when it is done cooking.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Turn on the TV and XBOX  | and connect  | them .  Open the disk tray of the XBOX  | and remove the video game disk from its case  | . Place the disk in the disk tray and close the tray  Place the disk in the disk tray and close  | the tray . Place the case on the table  | . Place a large bowl on the table  | .  Open the bag of chips  | and pour them into the bowl until it  | is full . Place the bag next to the bowl  | . Remove anything from the table  | that does not contain food  | . Place every XBOX controller on the table  | . Rotate the couches so that the backs face directly away from the TV  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the TV and XBOX and connect them.  Open the disk tray of the XBOX and remove the video game disk from its case. Place the disk in the disk tray and close the tray. Place the case on the table. Place a large bowl on the table.  Open the bag of chips and pour them into the bowl until it is full. Place the bag next to the bowl. Remove anything from the table that does not contain food. Place every XBOX controller on the table. Rotate the couches so that the backs face directly away from the TV.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take coffee from the container  | . Pour it into the mug  | . Grab spoon  | scoop the ice cream  | . Put the ice cream in to the mug  | . Pour syrup on to the ice cream  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take coffee from the container. Pour it into the mug. Grab spoon scoop the ice cream. Put the ice cream in to the mug. Pour syrup on to the ice cream.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Gather all cups, plates, mugs, and utensils  | and put them in the sink one at a time  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Gather all cups, plates, mugs, and utensils and put them in the sink one at a time.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Place ramen and instant ramen into pot and cook on top of the stove Place ramen and instant ramen into pot and cook on top of the stove  | . Put the chocolate and vanilla syrup bottle into the fridge  | and close the fridge door  | . Pour the drink into the long glass  | and serve ramen on the plate  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place ramen and instant ramen into pot and cook on top of the stove. Put the chocolate and vanilla syrup bottle into the fridge and close the fridge door. Pour the drink into the long glass and serve ramen on the plate. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Put all the pillows on the couch  | and then turn on the TV  | . Put the beer on the table in front of the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all the pillows on the couch and then turn on the TV. Put the beer on the table in front of the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Turn off the tv  | . Bring us the book and the bag of chips  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off the tv. Bring us the book and the bag of chips.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take coffee from the container  | . Pour coffee to the mug  | . Take  | the spoon scoop the ice cream  | . Put the ice cream in the mug  | . Pour syrup on the ice cream  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take coffee from the container. Pour coffee to the mug. Take the spoon scoop the ice cream. Put the ice cream in the mug. Pour syrup on the ice cream.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Prepare  | the coffee using hot water  | . Place two scoops of ice cream into the mug . Take the coffee  | and pour the coffee over the ice cream in the mug  | . Drizzle with syrup  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Prepare the coffee using hot water. Place two scoops of ice cream into the mug. Take the coffee and pour the coffee over the ice cream in the mug. Drizzle with syrup. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Microwave the coffee in the mug for 30 seconds .  Take a bowl  | . Using  | an ice cream scoop, add ice cream to the bowl twice an ice cream scoop, add  | ice cream to the bowl twice .  Retrieve the coffee mug  | and slowly pour the contents over the ice cream  | . Get the syrup  | .  Add two squirts of the bottle to the bowl  | .  Serve with a spoon  |  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Microwave the coffee in the mug for 30 seconds.  Take a bowl. Using an ice cream scoop, add ice cream to the bowl twice.  Retrieve the coffee mug and slowly pour the contents over the ice cream. Get the syrup.  Add two squirts of the bottle to the bowl.  Serve with a spoon </span> </sentence></point><point><email>mu63@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put game cd in xbox . Connect xbox to tv  | . Bring us bag of chips  | . Bring us the pillows  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put game cd in xbox. Connect xbox to tv. Bring us bag of chips. Bring us the pillows.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Gather all the cups, plates, mugs, pots, and utensils  | and put them in the sink one at a time  | . Gather the mustard and chocolate syrup  | and put it in the fridge  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Gather all the cups, plates, mugs, pots, and utensils and put them in the sink one at a time. Gather the mustard and chocolate syrup and put it in the fridge.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Put the trash bag into the bin  | . Place the pillows on the couch  | . Put the food on the center table  | . Turn the television  | and move  | to the desired channel  | to watch the movie  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the trash bag into the bin. Place the pillows on the couch. Put the food on the center table. Turn the television and move to the desired channel to watch the movie. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put the beer and coke into the garbage bag  | . Empty the contents of the bowl into the garbage bag  | . Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin |  Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin . Turn off the TV  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the beer and coke into the garbage bag. Empty the contents of the bowl into the garbage bag. Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin. Turn off the TV.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Get a pot  | and fill it with water from the faucet  | .  Place the pot on a burner of the stove  | and turn it  | on "medium ." Add the ramen to the water after ten minutes .  After the ramen is added,  | wait a few more minutes  | and then pour the contents of the pot slowly into a bowl  | . Serve with a fork  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get a pot and fill it with water from the faucet.  Place the pot on a burner of the stove and turn it on "medium." Add the ramen to the water after ten minutes.  After the ramen is added, wait a few more minutes and then pour the contents of the pot slowly into a bowl. Serve with a fork.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Place the Xbox and Xbox controllers  | onto the shelf in the corner . Turn of the television  | . Place the books on the table  | .Put the remote near the television  | . Throw away the beer  | . Bring the bowl and bag of chips to the center table  | and empty contents of chip bag into the bowl  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place the Xbox and Xbox controllers onto the shelf in the corner. Turn of the television. Place the books on the table.Put the remote near the television. Throw away the beer. Bring the bowl and bag of chips to the center table and empty contents of chip bag into the bowl. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Place pot on top of the stove  | and turn the stove  | on . wait for the water to boil  | . Get the ramen  | and empty contents into hot water into the pot  | . Cook  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place pot on top of the stove and turn the stove on. wait for the water to boil. Get the ramen and empty contents into hot water into the pot. Cook. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Turn off the TV  | . Bring books to the table in front of the couches . Empty the bag of chips into the bowl  | and bring the bowl to the table in front of the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off the TV. Bring books to the table in front of the couches. Empty the bag of chips into the bowl and bring the bowl to the table in front of the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Insert my gameCD into the DVD  | . Put my xbox and xbox controller on the table  | in front of the coach . Pour the chips into the bowl  | and put it on the table  | . Put away books onto a shelf  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Insert my gameCD into the DVD. Put my xbox and xbox controller on the table in front of the coach. Pour the chips into the bowl and put it on the table. Put away books onto a shelf. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kh523@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Bring the pillows to the couch  | . Empty the bag of chips into the bowl  | and put that on the table in front of the couch  | . Turn on the TV  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Bring the pillows to the couch. Empty the bag of chips into the bowl and put that on the table in front of the couch. Turn on the TV.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Turn off the television  | . Place the food into the trash bag  | and place trash bag into the bin  | . Place the pillows on the couch  | . Put the xbox and controllers  | away .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off the television. Place the food into the trash bag and place trash bag into the bin. Place the pillows on the couch. Put the xbox and controllers away. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Turn off the TV and the XBOX  | if applicable .  Move all controllers off of the coffee table  | .  Remove beer from the coffee table  | . Bring all books to the coffee table  | .  Bring the bowl of chips to the coffee table  | .  Open the bag of chips,  | and pour the contents into the bowl until it  | is full .  Move all chairs around the coffee table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off the TV and the XBOX if applicable.  Move all controllers off of the coffee table.  Remove beer from the coffee table. Bring all books to the coffee table.  Bring the bowl of chips to the coffee table.  Open the bag of chips, and pour the contents into the bowl until it is full.  Move all chairs around the coffee table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Cook the ramen in the pot with water  | . Serve the food on the plates  | and pour a drink into the long cups  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Cook the ramen in the pot with water. Serve the food on the plates and pour a drink into the long cups. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Move the couches on one side of the wall  | . Place the table and desk against another side of the wall  | . Pick up anything from the floor  | and place it  | to its designated location  | . Put the food on the counter  | . Empty the middle area  | . Turn on the music  | and increase the volume  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Move the couches on one side of the wall. Place the table and desk against another side of the wall. Pick up anything from the floor and place it to its designated location. Put the food on the counter. Empty the middle area. Turn on the music and increase the volume. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>take mug out the microwave  | and place two scoops of ice cream into the mug  | . pour the coffee on top  | . Drizzle with the vanilla syrup  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : take mug out the microwave and place two scoops of ice cream into the mug. pour the coffee on top. Drizzle with the vanilla syrup. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Put the pot of water onto the stove  | and turn the stove  | on . Get ramen and empty contents into pot  | . Cook  | . Serve on the plates  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the pot of water onto the stove and turn the stove on. Get ramen and empty contents into pot. Cook. Serve on the plates. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ng354@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Make breakfast  | . Pour the drink into a long cup  | . Serve the food in the plate  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Make breakfast. Pour the drink into a long cup. Serve the food in the plate. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Put XBOX controller  | by the XBOX .  Open the DVD case and XBOX disk tray  | . Place the DVD in the tray  | and close it  | . Leave the case near the XBOX  | .  Put all drinks on the coffee table  | .  Bring the bowl of chips to the coffee table  | . Open the chips,  | and pour them into the bowl  | until is is full .  Place the chips and bowl onto the coffee table  | .  Take all pillows and divide them evenly among the chairs  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put XBOX controller by the XBOX.  Open the DVD case and XBOX disk tray. Place the DVD in the tray and close it. Leave the case near the XBOX.  Put all drinks on the coffee table.  Bring the bowl of chips to the coffee table. Open the chips, and pour them into the bowl until is is full.  Place the chips and bowl onto the coffee table.  Take all pillows and divide them evenly among the chairs.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Insert the GameCD into the DVD  | . Put both xbox and xbox controller onto the table  | in front of the coaches . Put the TV remote on that table  | . Put the drinks and bowl in the middle of the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Insert the GameCD into the DVD. Put both xbox and xbox controller onto the table in front of the coaches. Put the TV remote on that table. Put the drinks and bowl in the middle of the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Throw away the open bag of chips  | . 
Put the Far Cry game CD back into its case  | .
Place the Xbox controller next to the console  | .
Pick up the book next to the television  | and put it back on the desk  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Throw away the open bag of chips. 
Put the Far Cry game CD back into its case.
Place the Xbox controller next to the console.
Pick up the book next to the television and put it back on the desk.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>clear all tables and the floor  | and put the contents on the shelves  | .  Take any drinks  | and put them on the coffee table  | .  Take the chip bowl  | and place it near the drinks  | . Open the chips,  | and pour them into the chip bowl until it  | is full . Place the bag near the bowl  | .  Change the TV channel until a dance music themed station  | is found  | .  Turn the volume  | to full .  Move all chairs and tables to the edge of the room  | .  Make sure the chairs are rotated so that they face the room's center  | .   .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : clear all tables and the floor and put the contents on the shelves.  Take any drinks and put them on the coffee table.  Take the chip bowl and place it near the drinks. Open the chips, and pour them into the chip bowl until it is full. Place the bag near the bowl.  Change the TV channel until a dance music themed station is found.  Turn the volume to full.  Move all chairs and tables to the edge of the room.  Make sure the chairs are rotated so that they face the room's center.  </span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take the coffee mug  | . Make sure it contains coffee  | .  If it contains coffee, put it in the microwave |   If it contains coffee, put it in the microwave .  Otherwise add coffee and water  | .  Microwave the mug for 2 minutes .  Get a bowl  | .  Using  | a n ice cream scoop, add ice cream to the bowl twice a n ice cream scoop, add  | ice cream to the bowl twice .  Slowly pour the contents of the mug into the bowl .  Add two squirts of the syrup  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the coffee mug. Make sure it contains coffee.  If it contains coffee, put it in the microwave.  Otherwise add coffee and water.  Microwave the mug for 2 minutes.  Get a bowl.  Using a n ice cream scoop, add ice cream to the bowl twice.  Slowly pour the contents of the mug into the bowl.  Add two squirts of the syrup.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put all dirty dishes into the sink, cups, plates, forks, the pot  | and all . Put ramen into the refrigerator  | . Put flavors in the cupboard  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all dirty dishes into the sink, cups, plates, forks, the pot and all. Put ramen into the refrigerator. Put flavors in the cupboard.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put the glasses and mugs into the sink  | . 
Put everything else into the fridge  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the glasses and mugs into the sink. 
Put everything else into the fridge.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Get a cup  | .  Open the fridge  | and remove milk  | . Close the fridge  | .  Slowly add milk to the cup  | until is is 7/8 full .  Get a bowl  | .  Add cereal to the bowl until it  | is full .  Slowly add milk to the cereal in the bowl  | .  Serve with a spoon  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get a cup.  Open the fridge and remove milk. Close the fridge.  Slowly add milk to the cup until is is 7/8 full.  Get a bowl.  Add cereal to the bowl until it is full.  Slowly add milk to the cereal in the bowl.  Serve with a spoon</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Run the gameCD . Put xbox and xbox  | controller on the table . Pour all the chips into the bowl  | and put the bowl on the table  | . Move drinks and food to the middle of the table  | . Put the pillow on the coach  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Run the gameCD. Put xbox and xbox controller on the table. Pour all the chips into the bowl and put the bowl on the table. Move drinks and food to the middle of the table. Put the pillow on the coach.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Pick up anything on the floor  | . Throw away the beer bottles  | . Pour chips into the bowl  | and place the bowl onto the table  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up anything on the floor. Throw away the beer bottles. Pour chips into the bowl and place the bowl onto the table. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Pour the pot  | and wash it in the sink  | .Fill the pot with water from the sink and boil it on the stove  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pour the pot and wash it in the sink.Fill the pot with water from the sink and boil it on the stove.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Pour the pot's contents into the trash  | and place all glasses and mugs into the sink  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pour the pot's contents into the trash and place all glasses and mugs into the sink.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Find the movie,  | open the case  | .  Open the XBOX disk tray  | .  Put the DVD in the tray  | and close it  | .  Turn on the TV  | .  Clear all non-food or drink items from the coffee table  | .  Bring all drink items to the coffee table  | .  Bring the bowl to the coffee table  | .  Open the bag of chips  | and pour the contents into the bowl until it's  | full .  Divide the pillows up evenly among the chairs  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Find the movie, open the case.  Open the XBOX disk tray.  Put the DVD in the tray and close it.  Turn on the TV.  Clear all non-food or drink items from the coffee table.  Bring all drink items to the coffee table.  Bring the bowl to the coffee table.  Open the bag of chips and pour the contents into the bowl until it's full.  Divide the pillows up evenly among the chairs.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put away the chocolate syrup  | . Place the glassware and mugs into the sink  | . Put the pots  | away .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put away the chocolate syrup. Place the glassware and mugs into the sink. Put the pots away. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Bring books to the room . If the television is on, turn it  | off . Pour the rest of the chips into the bowl,  | then throw away the bag  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Bring books to the room. If the television is on, turn it off. Pour the rest of the chips into the bowl, then throw away the bag. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>turn on TV and XBOX  | .  Remove CD from case  | and insert it into disk tray of XBOX  | .  Turn the TV volume  | up to full .  Remove all non-food and drink items  | and put them on shelves  | .  Bring all drinks to the coffee table  | . Bring the bowl to the coffee table  | .  Open the chips  | and pour them into the bowl until it  | is full . Move all chairs and tables so that they're against the walls  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : turn on TV and XBOX.  Remove CD from case and insert it into disk tray of XBOX.  Turn the TV volume up to full.  Remove all non-food and drink items and put them on shelves.  Bring all drinks to the coffee table. Bring the bowl to the coffee table.  Open the chips and pour them into the bowl until it is full. Move all chairs and tables so that they're against the walls.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put CDs and xbox  on the cupboard next to the TV  | . Put pillows onto the coaches  | . Put books on the shelf  | . Dump the bowl in the trash bag  | . Throw beer, coke and chips into the trash bag  | . Dispose the trash bag  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put CDs and xbox  on the cupboard next to the TV. Put pillows onto the coaches. Put books on the shelf. Dump the bowl in the trash bag. Throw beer, coke and chips into the trash bag. Dispose the trash bag.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>There's coffee in the mug on the table; take  | that, look in the freezer for some ice cream  | . Scoop some ice cream into the mug,  | then put vanilla syrup over it  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : There's coffee in the mug on the table; take that, look in the freezer for some ice cream. Scoop some ice cream into the mug, then put vanilla syrup over it. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Dump the contents of the mug down the sink  | .  Fill the pot with water from the faucet  | .  Put the pot on a burner on the stove on "medium" heat  | .  Add the ramen to the pot  | .  Wait fifteen minutes  | .  Slowly pour the contents of the pot into the mug .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Dump the contents of the mug down the sink.  Fill the pot with water from the faucet.  Put the pot on a burner on the stove on "medium" heat.  Add the ramen to the pot.  Wait fifteen minutes.  Slowly pour the contents of the pot into the mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Take the pot that already has some water in it  | . Put it on one of the burners,  | and turn it  | on .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the pot that already has some water in it. Put it on one of the burners, and turn it on. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Open the gameCD with TV  | . Put xbox and its controller on the table in front of the coaches  | . Pour chips into the bowl  | and throw the container into the trash bag  | . Put drinks and food on the middle of the table in front of coaches  | . Put pillows onto the coaches,  | one for each .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Open the gameCD with TV. Put xbox and its controller on the table in front of the coaches. Pour chips into the bowl and throw the container into the trash bag. Put drinks and food on the middle of the table in front of coaches. Put pillows onto the coaches, one for each. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>clear the table  | .  Bring all non-alcoholic drinks to the table  | .  Bring the bowl to the table  | . Open the chips  | and pour them into the bowl  | until it filled  | .  Bring all books to the table  | . Turn off the TV  | if needed  | .  Bring all chairs around the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : clear the table.  Bring all non-alcoholic drinks to the table.  Bring the bowl to the table. Open the chips and pour them into the bowl until it filled.  Bring all books to the table. Turn off the TV if needed.  Bring all chairs around the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Open the freezer,  | grab the ice cream  | inside . Prepare a mug with coffee,  | then pour the coffee into the white bowl on the counter  | . Put two scoops of ice cream into this white bowl,  | then put vanilla and chocolate syrup over it  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Open the freezer, grab the ice cream inside. Prepare a mug with coffee, then pour the coffee into the white bowl on the counter. Put two scoops of ice cream into this white bowl, then put vanilla and chocolate syrup over it. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Fill the pot with water from the sink  | . Pour ramen into the pot  | . Boil the pot on the stove  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the pot with water from the sink. Pour ramen into the pot. Boil the pot on the stove.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn on the television  | and put on a movie  | . Pour the chips into a bowl  | and put the bowl on the coffee table  | . Move all available pillows onto the couches  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the television and put on a movie. Pour the chips into a bowl and put the bowl on the coffee table. Move all available pillows onto the couches.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Put books on the table in front of the coaches .Turn off the TV  | . Put food and drinks on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put books on the table in front of the coaches.Turn off the TV. Put food and drinks on the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Get and open the instant ramen  | .  Add water from the faucet until it  | overflows .  Put instant ramen in the microwave  | .  turn the microwave on for two minutes  | .  Remove the instant ramen  | and serve with a fork  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get and open the instant ramen.  Add water from the faucet until it overflows.  Put instant ramen in the microwave.  turn the microwave on for two minutes.  Remove the instant ramen and serve with a fork</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>If any of the pots or dishes have food on or in them, dump  | them out in the garbage can, then put them in the sink  | . The syrups can go into the fridge,  | and the instant ramen should go back into a cabinet  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : If any of the pots or dishes have food on or in them, dump them out in the garbage can, then put them in the sink. The syrups can go into the fridge, and the instant ramen should go back into a cabinet. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Open the gameCD with TV  | . Put xbox and its controller on the low big table  | . Pour chips into the bowl  | and throw the container into the trash bag  | . Put drinks and food on the middle of the table in front of coaches  | . Put pillows onto the coaches,  | one for each . Arrange the coaches around the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Open the gameCD with TV. Put xbox and its controller on the low big table. Pour chips into the bowl and throw the container into the trash bag. Put drinks and food on the middle of the table in front of coaches. Put pillows onto the coaches, one for each. Arrange the coaches around the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Fill the pot with water,  | put it on the stove,  | and turn on the stove  | . When the water is boiling,  | put in the instant ramen  | . Fill a glass with water from the sink  | . 

Place everything onto the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the pot with water, put it on the stove, and turn on the stove. When the water is boiling, put in the instant ramen. Fill a glass with water from the sink. 

Place everything onto the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Add coffee to the mug  | and microwave it for 120 seconds  | .  Using a spoon add two cups of ice cream carefully to the mug  | .  Add one squirt of each chocolate and vanilla syrup to the mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Add coffee to the mug and microwave it for 120 seconds.  Using a spoon add two cups of ice cream carefully to the mug.  Add one squirt of each chocolate and vanilla syrup to the mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Take out the trash  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take out the trash.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put  | all used dishes into the sink  | . Put away water, ramen, and flavors in the cupboard  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all used dishes into the sink. Put away water, ramen, and flavors in the cupboard.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Pick up the beer bottle off the ground,  | throw it  | away . Turn off the television  | . Move the two seats away from the desk  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the beer bottle off the ground, throw it away. Turn off the television. Move the two seats away from the desk. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on the music  | . Place beer and chips onto the table  | . Pour chips into the bowl . Move all furniture to the sides of the room  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the music. Place beer and chips onto the table. Pour chips into the bowl. Move all furniture to the sides of the room. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Fill the pot with water from the sink and boil it on the stove  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the pot with water from the sink and boil it on the stove.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>vas59@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn  | on and connect the TV and XBOX  | .  Add the CD to the disk tray of the XBOX  | .  Turn the volume on the TV up all the way  | .  Move the tables and chair so that they are on the wall  | .  Clear the tables and chairs  | and put the contents on the shelves  | .  Move all drinks to the coffee table  | .  Fill the bowl with chips  | .  Bring the bowl to the coffee table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on and connect the TV and XBOX.  Add the CD to the disk tray of the XBOX.  Turn the volume on the TV up all the way.  Move the tables and chair so that they are on the wall.  Clear the tables and chairs and put the contents on the shelves.  Move all drinks to the coffee table.  Fill the bowl with chips.  Bring the bowl to the coffee table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Grab the ramen on the table  | . Go to the sink,  | fill the ramen cup with water  | up to the indicated line  | . Put into the microwave and microwave for 3 minutes |  Put into the microwave and microwave for 3 minutes .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grab the ramen on the table. Go to the sink, fill the ramen cup with water up to the indicated line. Put into the microwave and microwave for 3 minutes. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Open the gameCD with TV  | . Put xbox and its controller in the shelf under the TV  | . Pour chips into the bowl  | and throw the container into the trash bag  | . Put drinks and food on the middle of the table in front of coaches  | . Put pillows onto the coaches,  | one for each . Arrange coaches around the big table . Put books on the study desk  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Open the gameCD with TV. Put xbox and its controller in the shelf under the TV. Pour chips into the bowl and throw the container into the trash bag. Put drinks and food on the middle of the table in front of coaches. Put pillows onto the coaches, one for each. Arrange coaches around the big table. Put books on the study desk.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Take out the trash  | . Change the channel so a movie is playing  | .  Put food on the table  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take out the trash. Change the channel so a movie is playing.  Put food on the table. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Boil some water  | and make some coffee  | . Find a white bowl  | . Take ice cream out of the freezer  | . Put coffee into the white bowl,  | then put two scoops of ice cream  | over that . Finally, take the syrup on the counter  | and drizzle it over the ice cream  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Boil some water and make some coffee. Find a white bowl. Take ice cream out of the freezer. Put coffee into the white bowl, then put two scoops of ice cream over that. Finally, take the syrup on the counter and drizzle it over the ice cream. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn on the television,  | change the channel until you find a movie  | . Take the bowl  | and pour the chips into it;  | throw away the bag  | afterwards . Take out the trash  | . Put all available pillows on the couches  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the television, change the channel until you find a movie. Take the bowl and pour the chips into it; throw away the bag afterwards. Take out the trash. Put all available pillows on the couches. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>aw539@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put the game into the Xbox,  | connect xbox to television  | . Turn on the television  | . Move the couch so that it's in front of the Xbox  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the game into the Xbox, connect xbox to television. Turn on the television. Move the couch so that it's in front of the Xbox. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Boil some water with the pot  | and pour water into a clean mug  | . Get coffee from the cupboard  | and pour it into the mug  | . Stir the mug with a clean spoon for half a minute  | . Add ice cream and chocolate syrup into the mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Boil some water with the pot and pour water into a clean mug. Get coffee from the cupboard and pour it into the mug. Stir the mug with a clean spoon for half a minute. Add ice cream and chocolate syrup into the mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Open the gameCD with TV  | . Put xbox and its controller on the table in front of the coaches  | . Pour chips into the bowl  | and throw the container into the trash bag  | . Put drinks and food on the middle of the table in front of coaches  | . Arrange coaches around the big table . Put pillows onto the coaches,  | one for each .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Open the gameCD with TV. Put xbox and its controller on the table in front of the coaches. Pour chips into the bowl and throw the container into the trash bag. Put drinks and food on the middle of the table in front of coaches. Arrange coaches around the big table. Put pillows onto the coaches, one for each. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Fill the pot with water from the sink  | and add ramen to the pot  | . Heat the pot on the stove until the water boils for two minutes  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the pot with water from the sink and add ramen to the pot. Heat the pot on the stove until the water boils for two minutes.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Open the gameCD with TV  | . Put xbox and its controller on the table in front of the coaches  | . Pour chips into the bowl  | and throw the container into the trash bag  | . Put drinks and food on the middle of the table in front of coaches  | . Put pillows onto the coaches,  | one for each .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Open the gameCD with TV. Put xbox and its controller on the table in front of the coaches. Pour chips into the bowl and throw the container into the trash bag. Put drinks and food on the middle of the table in front of coaches. Put pillows onto the coaches, one for each. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Fill the mug with water from the sink  | and put it into the microwave oven  | . Turn on the oven  | for 10minutes .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the mug with water from the sink and put it into the microwave oven. Turn on the oven for 10minutes.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Fill the pot with water up to tow thirds and boil it on the stove for 10 minutes  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the pot with water up to tow thirds and boil it on the stove for 10 minutes.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kt454@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Pour the pot  | and wash it in the sink  | . Fill the pot with water up to two thirds  | . Heat it on the stove for 10 minutes  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pour the pot and wash it in the sink. Fill the pot with water up to two thirds. Heat it on the stove for 10 minutes</span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Collect all plates, cups, mugs, pot, and silverware  | and place them in the sink  | . Empty all cups, mugs, and the pot into the sink  | . Take the syrup bottles  | and place them in the refrigerator  | . Take the ramen  | and place it in the cabinet  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Collect all plates, cups, mugs, pot, and silverware and place them in the sink. Empty all cups, mugs, and the pot into the sink. Take the syrup bottles and place them in the refrigerator. Take the ramen and place it in the cabinet.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Pick up all cans, bottles, and garbage  | and put it in the trash can  | . Dump the contents of the bowl into the trash  | and place it in the sink in the kitchen  | . Take the trash bag  | outside . Place the CD, xbox, and controller in the cabinet under the TV  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up all cans, bottles, and garbage and put it in the trash can. Dump the contents of the bowl into the trash and place it in the sink in the kitchen. Take the trash bag outside. Place the CD, xbox, and controller in the cabinet under the TV.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Take all silverware, plates, cups, and pots  | and place them in the sink  | . Empty the contents of the cups and pot  | . Place the syrup bottles in the refrigerator  | . Put the ramen in the cabinet  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take all silverware, plates, cups, and pots and place them in the sink. Empty the contents of the cups and pot. Place the syrup bottles in the refrigerator. Put the ramen in the cabinet.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Dump the bowl into the trash  | and take the bowl to the kitchen  | and put it in the sink  | . Take all cans, bottles, and garbage  | and put it in the trash  | . Take the garbage bag  | outside .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Dump the bowl into the trash and take the bowl to the kitchen and put it in the sink. Take all cans, bottles, and garbage and put it in the trash. Take the garbage bag outside. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Pick up all books  | and place them on the shelf  | . Take all bottles, cans, and garbage  | and place them in the trash  | . Take the trash bag  | outside . Put the CD's, controller, and xbox in the cabinet  | . Take the pillows on the shelf  | and put them on the couches  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up all books and place them on the shelf. Take all bottles, cans, and garbage and place them in the trash. Take the trash bag outside. Put the CD's, controller, and xbox in the cabinet. Take the pillows on the shelf and put them on the couches.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Dump the bowl into the trash  | and place it in the sink in the kitchen  | . Take all cans, bottles, and garbage  | and put it in the trash  | . Take the trash bag  | outside . Place all books on the shelf  | . Turn on the xbox  | and play some music  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Dump the bowl into the trash and place it in the sink in the kitchen. Take all cans, bottles, and garbage and put it in the trash. Take the trash bag outside. Place all books on the shelf. Turn on the xbox and play some music.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Turn off the TV  | . Place anything related to the xbox in the cabinet under the TV  | . Dump the bowl into the trash  | and take the bowl  | and place it in the sink in the kitchen  | . Place all cans, bottles, and garbage in the trash  | . Take the trash bag  | outside .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off the TV. Place anything related to the xbox in the cabinet under the TV. Dump the bowl into the trash and take the bowl and place it in the sink in the kitchen. Place all cans, bottles, and garbage in the trash. Take the trash bag outside. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Turn off the TV  | . Dump the bowl in the trash  | and put it in the sink in the kitchen  | . Take all cans, bottles, and trash  | and put it in the trash can  | . Take the trash bag  | and put it  | outside . Take the remote off the chair  | and place it on the table  | . Take everything  | related to the xbox  | and put it in the cabinet under the TV  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off the TV. Dump the bowl in the trash and put it in the sink in the kitchen. Take all cans, bottles, and trash and put it in the trash can. Take the trash bag and put it outside. Take the remote off the chair and place it on the table. Take everything related to the xbox and put it in the cabinet under the TV.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Take all plates, cups, pots, and silverware  | and put them in the sink  | . Take all syrup bottles  | and place them in the fridge  | . Take a pot out of the cabinet  | and fill it with water  | . Put it on the back burner and boil the water  | . Open the ramen  | and pour in enough water  | . Take a cup out of the cabinet  | and pour the ginger ale on the counter into it  | . Give the ramen and ginger ale to who wants it  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take all plates, cups, pots, and silverware and put them in the sink. Take all syrup bottles and place them in the fridge. Take a pot out of the cabinet and fill it with water. Put it on the back burner and boil the water. Open the ramen and pour in enough water. Take a cup out of the cabinet and pour the ginger ale on the counter into it. Give the ramen and ginger ale to who wants it.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Place the ice cream in the freezer  | . Place all syrup bottles in the fridge  | . Take all pots, cups, plates, and silverware  | and put them in the sink  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place the ice cream in the freezer. Place all syrup bottles in the fridge. Take all pots, cups, plates, and silverware and put them in the sink. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Turn off the TV  | . Empty the bowl into the trash  | and take it to the kitchen  | . Take anything  | related to the xbox  | and put it in the cabinet under the TV  | . Put all books on the shelf  | . Put cans and bottles in the trash  | . Take the trash bag  | outside .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off the TV. Empty the bowl into the trash and take it to the kitchen. Take anything related to the xbox and put it in the cabinet under the TV. Put all books on the shelf. Put cans and bottles in the trash. Take the trash bag outside.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take the icecream out of the freezer  | and put several scoops in the cup with the coffee in it  | . Put chocolate and vanilla syrup on top  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the icecream out of the freezer and put several scoops in the cup with the coffee in it. Put chocolate and vanilla syrup on top.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Take the pot,  | fill it halfway with water,  | put in on the right burner  | and turn it  | on . Wait  | until the water is boiling,  | and then take the egg from the fridge  | and place it in the pot for 3 minutes  | . Take the egg out of the pot,  | place it in the bowl,  | and then take a cup from the counter  | and fill it with cold water from the sink  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the pot, fill it halfway with water, put in on the right burner and turn it on. Wait until the water is boiling, and then take the egg from the fridge and place it in the pot for 3 minutes. Take the egg out of the pot, place it in the bowl, and then take a cup from the counter and fill it with cold water from the sink. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Boil some water in a clean pot  | . Open the ramen  | and put enough water  | in .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Boil some water in a clean pot. Open the ramen and put enough water in.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Dump the bowl into the trash  | and take the bowl to the kitchen  | . Take cans, bottles, and trash  | and put it in the trash can  | . Put all books on the shelf  | . Take out the trash  | . Take the pillows off the shelf  | and put them on the couch  | . Turn all chairs  | to face the TV  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Dump the bowl into the trash and take the bowl to the kitchen. Take cans, bottles, and trash and put it in the trash can. Put all books on the shelf. Take out the trash. Take the pillows off the shelf and put them on the couch. Turn all chairs to face the TV.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Fill a clean pot with water and boil it  | . Open the ramen  | and put enough water  | in .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill a clean pot with water and boil it. Open the ramen and put enough water in.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Take the boiled egg out of the fridge,  | place it on the plate  | . Fill the cup with energy drink until halfway  | full, and then serve both the egg and the cup  | . Also, bring the salt shaker  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the boiled egg out of the fridge, place it on the plate. Fill the cup with energy drink until halfway full, and then serve both the egg and the cup. Also, bring the salt shaker. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Take all bottles, cans, and trash  | and put them in the trash can  | . Put everything  | related to the xbox on the shelf  | . Dump the bowl into the trash  | and take the bowl to the kitchen  | . Take the trash bag  | outside . Put all textbooks on the center table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take all bottles, cans, and trash and put them in the trash can. Put everything related to the xbox on the shelf. Dump the bowl into the trash and take the bowl to the kitchen. Take the trash bag outside. Put all textbooks on the center table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put the ramen in the cabinet  | . Put the syrups into the fridge  | . Take all cups, plates, bowls, pots, and silverware  | and put them into the sink  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the ramen in the cabinet. Put the syrups into the fridge. Take all cups, plates, bowls, pots, and silverware and put them into the sink. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take the ice cream out of the freezer  | and put several scoops into the cup with the coffee in it  | . Pour chocolate and vanilla syrup on top  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the ice cream out of the freezer and put several scoops into the cup with the coffee in it. Pour chocolate and vanilla syrup on top.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Take the pot on the counter  | and fill it with water  | . Boil it  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the pot on the counter and fill it with water. Boil it.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Change the channel  | to channel  | 5 . Fill the bowl with chips  | and bring it to the coffee table  | . Take the pillow from the shelf  | and bring it to the couch  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Change the channel to channel 5. Fill the bowl with chips and bring it to the coffee table. Take the pillow from the shelf and bring it to the couch. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>katey.huddleston@gmail.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Dump the bowl into the trash  | and take the bowl and the plate to the kitchen  | . Take all bottles, cans, and trash  | and put them in the trash can  | . Put all books on the shelf  | . Take the trash bag  | outside . Put the xbox in front of the TV  | and put in the game  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Dump the bowl into the trash and take the bowl and the plate to the kitchen. Take all bottles, cans, and trash and put them in the trash can. Put all books on the shelf. Take the trash bag outside. Put the xbox in front of the TV and put in the game.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Bring me the coffee from the microwave  | . Bring me the boiled egg from the fridge on a plate  | . Serve them to me at the counter  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Bring me the coffee from the microwave. Bring me the boiled egg from the fridge on a plate. Serve them to me at the counter. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Take  | pot,  | fill it with water from the sink,  | and put in on the burner  | . Turn the burner  | on, and wait until the water  | boils .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take pot, fill it with water from the sink, and put in on the burner. Turn the burner on, and wait until the water boils. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Dispose of trash .
Dispose of can .
Place Guiness Book on table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Dispose of trash.
Dispose of can.
Place Guiness Book on table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Collect all books from the room  | and place them on the coffee table  | . Turn off the TV  | and put away the xbox  | . Place chips in the bowl  | and put it on the coffee table  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Collect all books from the room and place them on the coffee table. Turn off the TV and put away the xbox. Place chips in the bowl and put it on the coffee table. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Place game in xbox  | .
Turn on xbox  | .
Place food on table  | .
Move couch in front of Television  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place game in xbox.
Turn on xbox.
Place food on table.
Move couch in front of Television.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Take  | pot  | . Fill it with water from the sink  | . Put it on the already lit  | burner . Wait  | until it boils .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take pot. Fill it with water from the sink. Put it on the already lit burner. Wait until it boils. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Pick up Long Cup2  | and carry it to the tap  | . Fill Long Cup2 with water  | . 
Open Refrigerator, take out food  | . Place in Microwave and heat  | . Place food on plate  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up Long Cup2 and carry it to the tap. Fill Long Cup2 with water. 
Open Refrigerator, take out food. Place in Microwave and heat. Place food on plate.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Remove the xbox from the desk  | . Place all  books in room on the desk  | . Place chips in bowl  | . Turn off tv  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Remove the xbox from the desk. Place all  books in room on the desk. Place chips in bowl. Turn off tv. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Pick up the CD  | and put it in the xbox  | .
Open both drinks on the table  | .
Dispose of trash in the trash can .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the CD and put it in the xbox.
Open both drinks on the table.
Dispose of trash in the trash can.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put the game in the xbox  | and turn it  | on . Connect the xbox to the tv,  | and turn  | both on . Put the chips in the bowl  | and put it on the table  | . Bring all the drinks in the room  | and put them on the table  | . Put all pillows on the couch  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the game in the xbox and turn it on. Connect the xbox to the tv, and turn both on. Put the chips in the bowl and put it on the table. Bring all the drinks in the room and put them on the table. Put all pillows on the couch. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put the game in the xbox  | .
Place the xbox in front of the television  | .
Place the bottle on the table  | .
Move the couch in front of the television  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the game in the xbox.
Place the xbox in front of the television.
Place the bottle on the table.
Move the couch in front of the television.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Organize the chairs so that they face the TV  | . Put the pillows on the chairs  | . Put the chips in the bowl  | . Turn  | to channel 3 on the TV  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Organize the chairs so that they face the TV. Put the pillows on the chairs. Put the chips in the bowl. Turn to channel 3 on the TV</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Get instant ramen cup  | . Fill up with water from the sink to the right amount  | . Put in microwave,  | and cook  | for specified time  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get instant ramen cup. Fill up with water from the sink to the right amount. Put in microwave, and cook for specified time. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Take the ramen  | and remove the top,  | and fill the cup with water  | . Place the ramen in the microwave and heat  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the ramen and remove the top, and fill the cup with water. Place the ramen in the microwave and heat.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Take the book off the shelf  | and place it on the table  | . Turn off the TV  | . Place bowl of food on the table .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the book off the shelf and place it on the table. Turn off the TV. Place bowl of food on the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Bring energy drink from the fridge . Bring boiled egg from the fridge  | . Put energy drink in class and egg on plate .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Bring energy drink from the fridge. Bring boiled egg from the fridge. Put energy drink in class and egg on plate. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Put CD into TV  | to watch movie  | . Bring chips and place in bowl on coffee table . Take pillows  | and put them on the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put CD into TV to watch movie. Bring chips and place in bowl on coffee table. Take pillows and put them on the couch</span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Pick up the mug  | and fill it with water from the refrigerator  | . Take out food from the refrigerator,  | place it on a plate  | and then heat it in the microwave  | . Place the mug and plate on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the mug and fill it with water from the refrigerator. Take out food from the refrigerator, place it on a plate and then heat it in the microwave. Place the mug and plate on the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on TV  | to channel  | 6 .  Push coffee table against wall . Push chairs against wall . Put chips  | in bowl and serve .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on TV to channel 6.  Push coffee table against wall. Push chairs against wall. Put chips in bowl and serve. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Pick up the mug of coffee  | and pour it on a plate  | . Open the refrigerator  | and scoop some ice cream onto the plate  | . Take the syrup bottle  | and squeeze some on the plate  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the mug of coffee and pour it on a plate. Open the refrigerator and scoop some ice cream onto the plate. Take the syrup bottle and squeeze some on the plate.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn tv on to channel  | 5 . Clean up xbox and xbox controller . Push all furniture against wall . put all drinks on end table,  | and fill bowl with chips  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn tv on to channel 5. Clean up xbox and xbox controller. Push all furniture against wall. put all drinks on end table, and fill bowl with chips. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Clean all dishes in the sink . Place ramen in cabinet  | . Place syrup in the fridge  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Clean all dishes in the sink. Place ramen in cabinet. Place syrup in the fridge. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Take  | pot,  | fill with water,  | put on burner,  | and turn burner  | on, wait until water boils  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take pot, fill with water, put on burner, and turn burner on, wait until water boils. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Take the CD  | and put it in the xbox  | . Place the bag of chips and the bottle on the low table  | . Dispose of trash .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the CD and put it in the xbox. Place the bag of chips and the bottle on the low table. Dispose of trash.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on the television  | to channel  | three .
put the coke and the bag of chips on the table  | . Put beer_1 under the table  | .
Move each table to a corner of the room  | . Move all the sofas or chairs next to the wall  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the television to channel three.
put the coke and the bag of chips on the table. Put beer_1 under the table.
Move each table to a corner of the room. Move all the sofas or chairs next to the wall.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Put egg on plate  | . Bring me plate with egg on it  | . Bring me a coke  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put egg on plate. Bring me plate with egg on it. Bring me a coke. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Take all dishes out of the sink  | and place them on the counter  | . Put all bottles in the refrigerator  | . Turn off the stove  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take all dishes out of the sink and place them on the counter. Put all bottles in the refrigerator. Turn off the stove.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put everything on the table onto the shelves  | . Place chip bag in garbage  | bag . Take out garbage  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put everything on the table onto the shelves. Place chip bag in garbage bag. Take out garbage. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>awa28@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn on TV  | . Turn  | to channel  | 3 . Bring chips in bowl and place on coffee table . Bring pillows from shelf and place on couches .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on TV. Turn to channel 3. Bring chips in bowl and place on coffee table. Bring pillows from shelf and place on couches. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take the mug out of the microwave  | and pour it on the plate  | . Take ice cream out of the freezer  | and scoop some onto the plate  | . Pick up the bottle of syrup  | and squeeze some on the plate  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the mug out of the microwave and pour it on the plate. Take ice cream out of the freezer and scoop some onto the plate. Pick up the bottle of syrup and squeeze some on the plate.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Put the book on the table  | .
Shut down the TV  | .
Put away the coke and the beer  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the book on the table.
Shut down the TV.
Put away the coke and the beer.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take the mug out of the microwave  | and pour it in the bigger plate  | . Take the ice cream out of the freezer  | and scoop some onto the same plate  | . Pick up the bottle of syrup  | and squeeze some onto the bigger plate  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the mug out of the microwave and pour it in the bigger plate. Take the ice cream out of the freezer and scoop some onto the same plate. Pick up the bottle of syrup and squeeze some onto the bigger plate.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Put the pot on the stove  | .
Turn on the stove until the water is 100 degrees  | celcius . Turn off the stove  | .
 .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the pot on the stove.
Turn on the stove until the water is 100 degrees celcius. Turn off the stove.
</span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Pick up the game  | and put it in the xbox  | . Take the bag of chips and the bowl  | and place them on the coffee table  | . Move the couch closer to the television  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the game and put it in the xbox. Take the bag of chips and the bowl and place them on the coffee table. Move the couch closer to the television.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Pick up the CD  | and put it in the xbox  | . Make sure all food is on the coffee table  | . Dispose of trash and place bottle on the coffee table .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the CD and put it in the xbox. Make sure all food is on the coffee table. Dispose of trash and place bottle on the coffee table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Pick up the pot  | and put it under the faucet  | . Fill the pot with water  | . Place the pot on the stove  | . Turn on the stove  | . Turn off the stove  | when the water is boiling  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the pot and put it under the faucet. Fill the pot with water. Place the pot on the stove. Turn on the stove. Turn off the stove when the water is boiling.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take the mug  | and pour its contents on a plate  | . Take ice cream out of the freezer  | and scoop some onto the same plate  | . Pick up the bottle of syrup  | and put some on the scooped ice cream  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the mug and pour its contents on a plate. Take ice cream out of the freezer and scoop some onto the same plate. Pick up the bottle of syrup and put some on the scooped ice cream.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>put pot in the sink  | and toggle the tap until the pot is 80 percent  | full . Then put the pot on the stove  | and turn on the stove  | . turn on the stove until water temperature is 100 degrees  | celcius .
Close the Microwave  | and turn on for four minutes  | . Then turn off the microwave  | and remove the mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : put pot in the sink and toggle the tap until the pot is 80 percent full. Then put the pot on the stove and turn on the stove. turn on the stove until water temperature is 100 degrees celcius.
Close the Microwave and turn on for four minutes. Then turn off the microwave and remove the mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Pick up the Instant Ramen  | and take off the top  | . Fill the container with water from the faucet  | . Put the container in the microwave  | and turn on the microwave  | . Turn off the microwave after a few minutes  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the Instant Ramen and take off the top. Fill the container with water from the faucet. Put the container in the microwave and turn on the microwave. Turn off the microwave after a few minutes.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Take the CD  | and put it in the xbox  | . Place the bowl and the chips on the table in front of the couch  | . Dispose of trash .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the CD and put it in the xbox. Place the bowl and the chips on the table in front of the couch. Dispose of trash.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>lrm96@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Place the bowl of food on the table in front of the couch  | . Make sure the TV  | is off . Make sure there is a book on the table in front of the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place the bowl of food on the table in front of the couch. Make sure the TV is off. Make sure there is a book on the table in front of the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Turn off the TV  | .
Put the Bag of Chips on the shelf  | . Also, put the beer, the coke and the bowl on the shelf  | .
Look for books  | and if you find any put them on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off the TV.
Put the Bag of Chips on the shelf. Also, put the beer, the coke and the bowl on the shelf.
Look for books and if you find any put them on the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Put the pot on the stove  | and turn on the stove  | . wait until the water has a temperature of 100 degrees Celsius  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the pot on the stove and turn on the stove. wait until the water has a temperature of 100 degrees Celsius.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Put the pot in the sink  | and turn on the tap until the pot is ten percent  | full . Then turn of the tap  | .
Put ramen in the pot  | and put the pot on the stove  | . turn on the stove for two minutes then turn it off .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the pot in the sink and turn on the tap until the pot is ten percent full. Then turn of the tap.
Put ramen in the pot and put the pot on the stove. turn on the stove for two minutes then turn it off. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take the mug of coffee  | and add ice cream to it  | . Then, add chocolate syrup to the mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the mug of coffee and add ice cream to it. Then, add chocolate syrup to the mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Place the book on the shelf  | .
Put the Xbox on the table next to the lamp  | .
Put garbage bag in the garbage bin  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place the book on the shelf.
Put the Xbox on the table next to the lamp.
Put garbage bag in the garbage bin </span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Take the ramen  | and add it to the pot  | . put the pot in the sink  | and turn on the tap until the pot is ten percent  | full . Then, put the pot on the stove  | and turn on the stove for two minutes  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the ramen and add it to the pot. put the pot in the sink and turn on the tap until the pot is ten percent full. Then, put the pot on the stove and turn on the stove for two minutes.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn on the TV  | and scroll down to the movie channel  | .
Put the bowl on the table  | .
Put the pillow on the big chair  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the TV and scroll down to the movie channel.
Put the bowl on the table.
Put the pillow on the big chair</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put the garbage bag in the garbage bin | Put the garbage bag in the garbage bin .
Put all books on the shelf  | .
Place the Xbox on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the garbage bag in the garbage bin.
Put all books on the shelf.
Place the Xbox on the table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Place the plate on the main table
Open  | the bottle of Canada Dry and pour into the long glass the bottle of Canada Dry and pour into the long glass  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place the plate on the main table
Open the bottle of Canada Dry and pour into the long glass</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Make coffee if there is none  | . Look for ice cream  | and if you find any, add it to the coffee mug  | . Then add syrup to the mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Make coffee if there is none. Look for ice cream and if you find any, add it to the coffee mug. Then add syrup to the mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put the table in one corner  | . put the coke, beer and the bowl on the table  | .
Turn on the Xbox  | .
Bring the large couch one meter away from the TV
  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the table in one corner. put the coke, beer and the bowl on the table.
Turn on the Xbox.
Bring the large couch one meter away from the TV
</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Prepare ramen and place in the mug  | . Place the mug next to the plate on the kitchen table  | .
Put food on the plate  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Prepare ramen and place in the mug. Place the mug next to the plate on the kitchen table.
Put food on the plate.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Place the pot in the sink  | and turn on tap until the pot  | is 80 percent full then turn off the tap  | . Place the pot on the stove  | . Turn on the stove until the water temperature is 100 degrees  | celcius .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place the pot in the sink and turn on tap until the pot is 80 percent full then turn off the tap. Place the pot on the stove. Turn on the stove until the water temperature is 100 degrees celcius</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put all books of the shelf  | . Put the garbage bag in the garbage bin |  Put the garbage bag in the garbage bin .
Place the CD on the shelf  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all books of the shelf. Put the garbage bag in the garbage bin.
Place the CD on the shelf.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on the TV to a music channel  | .
Put the beer on the table  | . Put the table in one corner of the room  | .
Put all chairs next to the wall  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the TV to a music channel.
Put the beer on the table. Put the table in one corner of the room.
Put all chairs next to the wall.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dmn56@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Put all chairs next to the wall  | .
Put the table in one corner of the room  | .
change the TV channel to a music  | channel .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all chairs next to the wall.
Put the table in one corner of the room.
change the TV channel to a music channel</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Clear table  | by dumping contents of bowl in sink  | and throwing away beer and coke in trash  | . Take books from shelf  | and put them on the table  | . Take remote from shelf  | and turn off the TV,  | then replace remote on shelf  | . Throw out trash bag  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Clear table by dumping contents of bowl in sink and throwing away beer and coke in trash. Take books from shelf and put them on the table. Take remote from shelf and turn off the TV, then replace remote on shelf. Throw out trash bag. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Fill the pot with water  | and put it on the back right burner  | which is on . Open the ramen cup  | . When the water is boiling,  | pour it into the ramen cup  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the pot with water and put it on the back right burner which is on. Open the ramen cup. When the water is boiling, pour it into the ramen cup. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Arrange couches in front of the TV,  | put the Far Cry game inside the Xbox,  | turn on the TV and the Xbox,  | and put out Coke cans  | and open the chips bag  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Arrange couches in front of the TV, put the Far Cry game inside the Xbox, turn on the TV and the Xbox, and put out Coke cans and open the chips bag.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Take the dishes  | and place them on top  | of each other . Stack the cups  | . Put the bottles away in the appropriate cabinets  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the dishes and place them on top of each other. Stack the cups. Put the bottles away in the appropriate cabinets. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Pick up remote and switch channel to a music  | channel . Remove beer, bowl, and trash bag on floor  | and dispose  | . Clean bowl in kitchen, and place chips in bowl . Place bowl on table . Move chairs aside to the walls to make room  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up remote and switch channel to a music channel. Remove beer, bowl, and trash bag on floor and dispose. Clean bowl in kitchen, and place chips in bowl. Place bowl on table. Move chairs aside to the walls to make room. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put all the bowls, cups, pots, and utensils in the sink  | . Put perishable items in the refrigerator  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all the bowls, cups, pots, and utensils in the sink. Put perishable items in the refrigerator.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Take the red cup  | and fill it with water at the sink  | . Place the cup in the microwave  | and heat until it is the appropriate temperature  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the red cup and fill it with water at the sink. Place the cup in the microwave and heat until it is the appropriate temperature. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Take the mug in the microwave  | and go to the sink  | and add water to it  | . After there is water in the mug put the mug back in the microwave and set it to no more than 3 minutes  After there is water in the mug put the mug back in the microwave and set it to no more than 3 minutes  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the mug in the microwave and go to the sink and add water to it. After there is water in the mug put the mug back in the microwave and set it to no more than 3 minutes.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Place the game back in its case  | . Pick up the books  | and put them all on the desk  | . Put the cans, bottles, and chip bag in the trash bin  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place the game back in its case. Pick up the books and put them all on the desk. Put the cans, bottles, and chip bag in the trash bin.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Wash mug, long cups, spoon and bowl and place in cabinets . Wash pot and place on stove . Place chocolate and vanilla syrup, and ramen in pantry  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Wash mug, long cups, spoon and bowl and place in cabinets. Wash pot and place on stove. Place chocolate and vanilla syrup, and ramen in pantry. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Take a cup  | and fill it with water from the sink  | . Make ramen  | and put it in a plate  | . Take both items  | and serve  | them to whomever  | it is meant  | for .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take a cup and fill it with water from the sink. Make ramen and put it in a plate. Take both items and serve them to whomever it is meant for. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>take pot over to the sink,  | turn on the tap, and fill with water turn on the tap,  | and fill with water  | . Turn off the water  | . Take pot over to stove,  | place on any burner, and turn on the fire for that burner place on any burner,  | and turn on the fire for that burner  | . Wait  | . Once there is steam rising and bubbles,  | turn off fire  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : take pot over to the sink, turn on the tap, and fill with water. Turn off the water. Take pot over to stove, place on any burner, and turn on the fire for that burner. Wait. Once there is steam rising and bubbles, turn off fire. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Get the ice cream and the syrup from the counter  | and put it on the plate  | . Then get the mug with coffee in it  | and also place it by the plate with the ice cream and syrup  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the ice cream and the syrup from the counter and put it on the plate. Then get the mug with coffee in it and also place it by the plate with the ice cream and syrup.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn TV  | on with remote and find movie (Lincoln) | on with remote and find movie (Lincoln) . Take bag of chips  | and place on table  | . Take pillow from shelf and place on a sofa  | . Throw away beer and soda,  | and place Book of Records on shelf  | with brown book .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn TV on with remote and find movie (Lincoln). Take bag of chips and place on table. Take pillow from shelf and place on a sofa. Throw away beer and soda, and place Book of Records on shelf with brown book. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn the TV  | on and change the channel to one with music  | . Get food  | and put it on the coffee table  | . Pick up the controller on the floor and place on the table  | . Throw out the bottle  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn the TV on and change the channel to one with music. Get food and put it on the coffee table. Pick up the controller on the floor and place on the table. Throw out the bottle. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Make sure the TV  | is off first . Then get  | the books needed  | to study and put it on the table  | . Then take the chips bag  | and pour its contents inside the bowl  | next to it and bring the bowl to the table near the couches  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Make sure the TV is off first. Then get the books needed to study and put it on the table. Then take the chips bag and pour its contents inside the bowl next to it and bring the bowl to the table near the couches.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Take pot on counter  | and fill it with water from the sink  | . Place the pot on a burner on the stove  | . Turn on the burner  | and let the water boil  | . Once it is boiling,  | open the lid of the ramen cup  | and pour boiling water in until it reaches the top of the container  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take pot on counter and fill it with water from the sink. Place the pot on a burner on the stove. Turn on the burner and let the water boil. Once it is boiling, open the lid of the ramen cup and pour boiling water in until it reaches the top of the container.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Open fridge and freezer  | and pick a drink  | . Remove boiled egg  | as well and place on plate  | . Pour said drink in a long cup or mug  | . Bring cup, plate, and possibly salt to whomever is eating, with plate  | in one hand and drink in the other .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Open fridge and freezer and pick a drink. Remove boiled egg as well and place on plate. Pour said drink in a long cup or mug. Bring cup, plate, and possibly salt to whomever is eating, with plate in one hand and drink in the other. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Get the tall cup with water in it  | and put it in the microwave  | . Set the microwave for no more than 3 minutes  | . Then take the ramen on the counter  | and pour its contents in the cup  | that was in the microwave  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the tall cup with water in it and put it in the microwave. Set the microwave for no more than 3 minutes. Then take the ramen on the counter and pour its contents in the cup that was in the microwave.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Throw out the bottle, can and chips  | . Pick up the xbox and controller  | and place on coffee table  | . Stack the books neatly on the shelf  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Throw out the bottle, can and chips. Pick up the xbox and controller and place on coffee table. Stack the books neatly on the shelf. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Get the pillows  | and move them onto the couches  | . Then turn on the TV  | and put a movie inside the xbox  | . Move the xbox remote to the table in front of the couches  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the pillows and move them onto the couches. Then turn on the TV and put a movie inside the xbox. Move the xbox remote to the table in front of the couches.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Dump contents of mug, long cup, and pot in sink . Wash mug etc by soaping with sponge (robot waterproof?),  | turning on the water, rinsing, turning off water . Put mug and long cup with the plate  | . Put pot on sink  | . Put icecream in freezer (open door, place on shelf,  | close door) . Put syrup, ramen, and salt in pantry  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Dump contents of mug, long cup, and pot in sink. Wash mug etc by soaping with sponge (robot waterproof?), turning on the water, rinsing, turning off water. Put mug and long cup with the plate. Put pot on sink. Put icecream in freezer (open door, place on shelf, close door). Put syrup, ramen, and salt in pantry. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Bring xbox and controller closer to the TV  | and set  | up . Put the game  | in . Empty bowl and pour chips in . Place on coffee table  | . Get pillows from shelf  | and arrange on couch  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Bring xbox and controller closer to the TV and set up. Put the game in. Empty bowl and pour chips in. Place on coffee table. Get pillows from shelf and arrange on couch. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put away pillows,  | empty bowl,  | throw out drinks  | . Place controller with xbox  | . Put books on one shelf  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put away pillows, empty bowl, throw out drinks. Place controller with xbox. Put books on one shelf. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Go to the refrigerator and open it to get the boiled egg and the coke  | can can | can . Then go to the counter  | and get the plate  | and put the egg on the plate  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Go to the refrigerator and open it to get the boiled egg and the coke can. Then go to the counter and get the plate and put the egg on the plate.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>gather ingredients (egg from fridge, ramen from counter) microwave water in cup,  | or boil water in pot  | (process described in previous scenario)  | . Pour boiling water in ramen cup  | after opening the cup  | and removing soup base  | . pour soup base  | . Peel egg  | and add  | to ramen and throw shell in trash  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : gather ingredients (egg from fridge, ramen from counter) microwave water in cup, or boil water in pot (process described in previous scenario). Pour boiling water in ramen cup after opening the cup and removing soup base. pour soup base. Peel egg and add to ramen and throw shell in trash. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on TV  | and make sure the volume is up for music  | . Pour the chips into the bowl and place on coffee table  | . Take the xbox off the floor and place on shelf  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on TV and make sure the volume is up for music. Pour the chips into the bowl and place on coffee table. Take the xbox off the floor and place on shelf. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Take the dishes  | and stack  | neatly . Put the bottles in the appropriate cabinet  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the dishes and stack neatly. Put the bottles in the appropriate cabinet. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Open freezer,  | remove icecream,  | close freezer  | . Get spoon and plate,  | open ice cream,  | scoop  | and place on plate,  | close ice cream,  | replace in fridge  | . Get mug with coffee  | and pour over ice cream  | . Place mug in sink . Get chocolate syrup  | and pump over ice cream  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Open freezer, remove icecream, close freezer. Get spoon and plate, open ice cream, scoop and place on plate, close ice cream, replace in fridge. Get mug with coffee and pour over ice cream. Place mug in sink. Get chocolate syrup and pump over ice cream. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Turn off the TV,  | put all the pillows back on the top shelf,  | empty the contents of the bowl,  | throw out empty bottles and cans,  | and take out the trash  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off the TV, put all the pillows back on the top shelf, empty the contents of the bowl, throw out empty bottles and cans, and take out the trash.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Put coffee in the tall glass  | . Take out the ice cream and using a spoon, scoop some into the cup  | . Take the chocolate syrup  | and drizzle some on top  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put coffee in the tall glass. Take out the ice cream and using a spoon, scoop some into the cup. Take the chocolate syrup and drizzle some on top. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Throw out beer and coke  | . Throw out trash bag  | . Fluff pillows on couch  | and stand them up . Put Book of records on shelf with other books |  Put Book of records on shelf with other books .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Throw out beer and coke. Throw out trash bag. Fluff pillows on couch and stand them up. Put Book of records on shelf with other books. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Take the pot,  | place it under the sink  | and fill it with water  | . Put the pot on the stove  | and turn on its respective burner  | . Keep it on until the water comes to a boil  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the pot, place it under the sink and fill it with water. Put the pot on the stove and turn on its respective burner. Keep it on until the water comes to a boil.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Turn on xbox  | . Take Far Cry Game CD  | and put in xbox  | by pressig  | eject to open drive  | . Throw out beer, coke, and sketchy stuff in bowl  | . Take pillows from shelf  | and distribute among couches  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on xbox. Take Far Cry Game CD and put in xbox by pressig eject to open drive. Throw out beer, coke, and sketchy stuff in bowl. Take pillows from shelf and distribute among couches. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Set up the xbox  | and put  | in the desired movie  | to watch  | . Turn on the TV  | and xbox  | appropriately . Dump the bowl's contents  | and fill it with chips  | . Put the pillows on the couches up against the back cushion  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Set up the xbox and put in the desired movie to watch. Turn on the TV and xbox appropriately. Dump the bowl's contents and fill it with chips. Put the pillows on the couches up against the back cushion.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take ice cream from freezer  | and scoop with spoon into the mug with coffee in it  | . Replace ice cream in freezer  | . Take vanilla syrup  | and pour over icecream  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take ice cream from freezer and scoop with spoon into the mug with coffee in it. Replace ice cream in freezer. Take vanilla syrup and pour over icecream. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Take Book  | of Records and place on table with brown book  | . The TV is already turned  | off .Throw out open beer and coke  | . Chips are good .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take Book of Records and place on table with brown book. The TV is already turned off....Throw out open beer and coke. Chips are good. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Take Book  | of Records and place on table with brown book  | . The TV is already turned  | off .Throw out open beer and coke  | . Chips are good .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take Book of Records and place on table with brown book. The TV is already turned off....Throw out open beer and coke. Chips are good. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn on TV  | with remote and turn to Lincoln  | . Pour chips into the bowl next to it  | and put bowl on the table  | . Throw out coke and beer  | . Go to shelf  | and pick up pillows  | and distribute on couches  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on TV with remote and turn to Lincoln. Pour chips into the bowl next to it and put bowl on the table. Throw out coke and beer. Go to shelf and pick up pillows and distribute on couches. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Rearrange the couch seats around the coffee table  | . Place the bowl on the coffee table  | . Put all the books together on the desk  | . Throw out empty things  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Rearrange the couch seats around the coffee table. Place the bowl on the coffee table. Put all the books together on the desk. Throw out empty things. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Take boiled egg from fridge  | . Peel  | and throw out shell  | . Put on plate  | . Take plate along with the mug with coffee in it to hungry person  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take boiled egg from fridge. Peel and throw out shell. Put on plate. Take plate along with the mug with coffee in it to hungry person. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Keep all books together on the shelf  | . Make sure the tv  | is off . Put the chips on the coffee table  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Keep all books together on the shelf. Make sure the tv is off. Put the chips on the coffee table. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Take remote and turn channel to Lincoln  | . Pick up chips  | and tilt bag  | to pour chips into the bowl next to it  | . Bring the bowl over to table  | . Dispose of the chip bag . Dispose of coke and beer . Go to shelf  | and take pillows  | down . Take pillow over to couches  | and place on couch  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take remote and turn channel to Lincoln. Pick up chips and tilt bag to pour chips into the bowl next to it. Bring the bowl over to table. Dispose of the chip bag. Dispose of coke and beer. Go to shelf and take pillows down. Take pillow over to couches and place on couch. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Set up the xbox and tv  | and turn  | both on . Put the movie  | in . Put the chips on the table  | and dump the bowl  | . Put the pillows on the couch  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Set up the xbox and tv and turn both on. Put the movie in. Put the chips on the table and dump the bowl. Put the pillows on the couch. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Turn on the TV,  | put the video game in the xbox,  | arrange couches  | around the TV, put the chips inside the bowl  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the TV, put the video game in the xbox, arrange couches around the TV, put the chips inside the bowl.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Throw out chips, coke and beer  | . Take brown book and place on shelf with CD  | . Take xbox game controller  | and put with xbox  | . Take pillows from shelf  | and put on couches  | . Take bowl from floor and place in kitchen  | . Throw out the trash  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Throw out chips, coke and beer. Take brown book and place on shelf with CD. Take xbox game controller and put with xbox. Take pillows from shelf and put on couches. Take bowl from floor and place in kitchen. Throw out the trash. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Take the coffee out of the microwave  | . Pour the ramen into the bowl  | . Carry  | both and serve to whomever  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the coffee out of the microwave. Pour the ramen into the bowl. Carry both and serve to whomever. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Dump the coffee in the mug in the sink,  | put all perishable items in the refrigerator,  | put all the dishes, utensils, and pots in the sink  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Dump the coffee in the mug in the sink, put all perishable items in the refrigerator, put all the dishes, utensils, and pots in the sink. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kmc376@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Put the pot on the stove and boil the water  | . When boiling,  | place in the cup with instant ramen  | . Wait a few minutes  | for it to cook  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the pot on the stove and boil the water. When boiling, place in the cup with instant ramen. Wait a few minutes for it to cook. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Take glass  | and put water in glass via sink  | . Remove mug with coffee from microwave  | . Put glass in microwave  | . Once water is boiled/hot, remove from microwave  | . Open noodles  | and pour water in noodles  | . Wait  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take glass and put water in glass via sink. Remove mug with coffee from microwave. Put glass in microwave. Once water is boiled/hot, remove from microwave. Open noodles and pour water in noodles. Wait. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Make  | sure the TV is turned  | off, take the chips  | and pour its contents in the bowl,  | and arrange the needed books on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Make sure the TV is turned off, take the chips and pour its contents in the bowl, and arrange the needed books on the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Empty the contents of the mug  | and put the dirty dishes and utensils inside the sink  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Empty the contents of the mug and put the dirty dishes and utensils inside the sink.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ll538@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Turn off right back burner  | . Take ice cream from freezer  | and scoop with spoon  | and put in mug with coffee  | . Replace ice cream in freezer  | . Take vanilla syrup  | and pour over ice cream  | .   .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off right back burner. Take ice cream from freezer and scoop with spoon and put in mug with coffee. Replace ice cream in freezer. Take vanilla syrup and pour over ice cream.  </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put the game in the xbox,  | take the chips  | and pour its contents in the bowl,  | arrange the couches around the TV,  | turn on the TV,  | and place the xbox controller on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the game in the xbox, take the chips and pour its contents in the bowl, arrange the couches around the TV, turn on the TV, and place the xbox controller on the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Get the egg from the fridge  | and put it on the plate  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the egg from the fridge and put it on the plate.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Take the cup  | and pour water in it  | . Then put it in the microwave  | and heat it  | up .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the cup and pour water in it. Then put it in the microwave and heat it up.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Take the game  | and put it in the xbox,  | turn on the TV  | and arrange the couches around the TV  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the game and put it in the xbox, turn on the TV and arrange the couches around the TV.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Put the books on the table,  | turn off the TV  | and put food out on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the books on the table, turn off the TV and put food out on the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put the dishes in the sink,  | put all perishable foods in the refrigerator,  | and put the pots and utensils in the sink  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the dishes in the sink, put all perishable foods in the refrigerator, and put the pots and utensils in the sink.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ord5@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put the game in the xbox,  | turn on the TV,  | arrange the couches around the TV,  | take the chips  | and pour its content in the bowl,  | take the bowl  | and place it on the table by the couches  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the game in the xbox, turn on the TV, arrange the couches around the TV, take the chips and pour its content in the bowl, take the bowl and place it on the table by the couches.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put the xbox controller and food on the table in front of the couch  | . Put away the math book  | .   .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the xbox controller and food on the table in front of the couch. Put away the math book.  </span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Boil some water  | . Make coffee  | . Pour some water into a bowl  | and put the instant ramen in it  | . Wait for 3 minutes  | before serving it  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Boil some water. Make coffee. Pour some water into a bowl and put the instant ramen in it. Wait for 3 minutes before serving it. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Put CD  | in xbox1 and turn it  | on to play music  | . Pour the bag of chip into the bowl  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put CD in xbox1 and turn it on to play music. Pour the bag of chip into the bowl. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>put xbox and xboxController into the TV  | stand . Throw the trash bag into the garbage bin  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : put xbox and xboxController into the TV stand. Throw the trash bag into the garbage bin. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>place glass1, long cup2, long cup1, mug and canada dry on the table against the wall .  Put the spoon and plate into the sink  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : place glass1, long cup2, long cup1, mug and canada dry on the table against the wall.  Put the spoon and plate into the sink. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>place glass1, long cup2, long cup1, mug and canada dry on the table against the wall .  Put the spoon and plate into the sink  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : place glass1, long cup2, long cup1, mug and canada dry on the table against the wall.  Put the spoon and plate into the sink. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Fill the pot with water  | and put it on the stove  | . Boil the water  | . Put the instant ramen in the pot  | . Cook for 3 minutes  | . Wait  | until it is cool .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the pot with water and put it on the stove. Boil the water. Put the instant ramen in the pot. Cook for 3 minutes. Wait until it is cool. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Put the brown book on the coffee table  | . Turn off TV  | . Pour the bag of chip into the bowl  | and place it on the coffee table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the brown book on the coffee table. Turn off TV. Pour the bag of chip into the bowl and place it on the coffee table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Put the brown book on the coffee table  | . Turn off TV  | . Pour the bag of chip into the bowl  | and place it on the coffee table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the brown book on the coffee table. Turn off TV. Pour the bag of chip into the bowl and place it on the coffee table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Fill the pot with water from tap  | . Place it on the stove  | . Turn the stove  | on . Wait for water to boil  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the pot with water from tap. Place it on the stove. Turn the stove on. Wait for water to boil. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>grasp the coffee mug  | and put it near the fridge  | . Open the freezer  | and put a spoon of ice cream in the mug  | . Pour some syrup on top of the ice cream from vanilla syrup bottle |  Pour some syrup on top of the ice cream from vanilla syrup bottle .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp the coffee mug and put it near the fridge. Open the freezer and put a spoon of ice cream in the mug. Pour some syrup on top of the ice cream from vanilla syrup bottle. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>grab the beer, coke and bowl  | and place them on the coffee table  | . Grab pillows  | and put them on the couch  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grab the beer, coke and bowl and place them on the coffee table. Grab pillows and put them on the couch. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>move away the xbox1 and FarCryGameCD from the desk  | . Place the brown book on the desk  | . Turn off TV  | . Place the bag of chip and coke on the desk  | too .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : move away the xbox1 and FarCryGameCD from the desk. Place the brown book on the desk. Turn off TV. Place the bag of chip and coke on the desk too.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>move the mug close to the chocolate syrup  | . Take a spoon of ice cream from the freezer,  | and put it on top of the coffee  | . Pour some chocolate syrup  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : move the mug close to the chocolate syrup. Take a spoon of ice cream from the freezer, and put it on top of the coffee. Pour some chocolate syrup.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>helenjyun@gmail.com</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Take a scoop of ice cream  | and put it on the plate  | . Take the plate next to the mug  | . Put a spoon  | next to them too .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take a scoop of ice cream and put it on the plate. Take the plate next to the mug. Put a spoon next to them too. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>chenxiawu@cs.cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Grasp the pot  | and walk to the sink  | . Toggle the tap  | to fill the pot  | . Put the pot on the stove  | . Turn on the burner  | . Turn off the burner  | when the water is boiling  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grasp the pot and walk to the sink. Toggle the tap to fill the pot. Put the pot on the stove. Turn on the burner. Turn off the burner when the water is boiling. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>asheshjain399@gmail.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>empty mug, cup and glass in the sink,  | and then place them in cupboards  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : empty mug, cup and glass in the sink, and then place them in cupboards.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>asheshjain399@gmail.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>take mug form microwave  | and pour its contents in the sink  | . Do the same to the cup and glass  | . Finally put everything in the cupboard  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : take mug form microwave and pour its contents in the sink. Do the same to the cup and glass. Finally put everything in the cupboard.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>asheshjain399@gmail.com</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>get xbox from the shelf  | and place it on the table  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : get xbox from the shelf and place it on the table. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Take out the books  | for me and turn off the tv  | . Prepare some coffee for me with milk and sugar  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take out the books for me and turn off the tv. Prepare some coffee for me with milk and sugar.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put everything on the floor to the tables  | . Clean the floor .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put everything on the floor to the tables. Clean the floor.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>take the coffee  | and then mix with ice cream and syrup  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : take the coffee and then mix with ice cream and syrup</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>get out the ramen  | and then cook it  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : get out the ramen and then cook it</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>get the books  | and close the tv  | and prepare food  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : get the books and close the tv and prepare food</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>turn on the music  | to classical and prepare food like snacks fruits  | . clean  | the living room  | to get empty space  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : turn on the music to classical and prepare food like snacks fruits. clean the living room to get empty space.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yw348@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>-cake-egg-milk-serve .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : -cake-egg-milk-serve</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yw348@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>-drink-food-books-paper .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : -drink-food-books-paper</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yw348@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>-drink-food-books-paper .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : -drink-food-books-paper</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yw348@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>-movie-popcorn-drinks .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : -movie-popcorn-drinks</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yw348@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>-food-drinks-movie .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : -food-drinks-movie</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yw348@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>-take coffee-ice cream-milk-syrup .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : -take coffee-ice cream-milk-syrup</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yw348@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>-arrange things-trash waste .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : -arrange things-trash waste</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put all silverwear into the sink  | .
Put the ramen back into the ramen container | 
Put the ramen back into the ramen container . 
Put everything left on the counters  | onto a single counter .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all silverwear into the sink.
Put the ramen back into the ramen container. 
Put everything left on the counters onto a single counter.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Put  | all books required for our study night on the table  | . Turn off the TV  | . Put enough food for us on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all books required for our study night on the table. Turn off the TV. Put enough food for us on the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Add a scoop of icecream  | to the mug filled with coffee  | . Take the same mug  | and add three squeezes of syrup to it  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Add a scoop of icecream to the mug filled with coffee. Take the same mug and add three squeezes of syrup to it.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Fill the long cup with ramen  | . Read the instructions on the ramen container  | to find out the necessary amount of water and microwaving time  | . Add the water to the long cup and microwave  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the long cup with ramen. Read the instructions on the ramen container to find out the necessary amount of water and microwaving time. Add the water to the long cup and microwave.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put the xbox equipment inside the cupboard  | .  Put the mathbook next to the other books in the room  | . Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin |  Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the xbox equipment inside the cupboard.  Put the mathbook next to the other books in the room. Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Plug the Xbox into the TV  | . Make  | sure both are turned  | on . Put the CD with music into the Xbox  | . Run the Xbox with the music CD . Make sure the TV volume at 50%  | . Put  | the bowl filled with chips and bag of chips on the table | the bowl filled with chips and bag of chips on the table . Put the xbox equipment in the cupboard  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Plug the Xbox into the TV. Make sure both are turned on. Put the CD with music into the Xbox. Run the Xbox with the music CD. Make sure the TV volume at 50%. Put the bowl filled with chips and bag of chips on the table. Put the xbox equipment in the cupboard. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Connect the Xbox to the TV  | . Turn on the TV and Xbox  | . Find the Far Cry Game xbox  | game and put it into the xbox  | . Put  | the Bowl filled with chips on the table  | . Arrange the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Connect the Xbox to the TV. Turn on the TV and Xbox. Find the Far Cry Game xbox game and put it into the xbox. Put the Bowl filled with chips on the table. Arrange the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Place all dishes and utensils from the counter into the sink  | . Put the ramen on the counter into the original ramen container |  Put the ramen on the counter into the original ramen container . Put everything left on the kitchen counters  | onto one single counter .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Place all dishes and utensils from the counter into the sink. Put the ramen on the counter into the original ramen container. Put everything left on the kitchen counters onto one single counter.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put the utensils, cups, pots, plates into the sink  | . Put the frozen foods into the freezer  | .
Place everything else onto one single counter  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the utensils, cups, pots, plates into the sink. Put the frozen foods into the freezer.
Place everything else onto one single counter.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Prepare the Ramen in a long cup and microwave  | . Fill the mug with water  | . Bring it  | to me .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Prepare the Ramen in a long cup and microwave. Fill the mug with water. Bring it to me.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Fill the ramen container  | with the required amount of ramen  | and place the container into the microwave  | for the required amount of time  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the ramen container with the required amount of ramen and place the container into the microwave for the required amount of time.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take the mug  | and add coffee  | . Place a scoop of icecream from the freezer and syrup into it  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the mug and add coffee. Place a scoop of icecream from the freezer and syrup into it.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put the Xbox and controller inside the cupboard under the TV  | . Place all edibles on the table  | . Put all CDs and books on the shelves  | . Put the pillows on the shelves  | as well . Put the trash bag in the trash pin |  Put the trash bag in the trash pin .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the Xbox and controller inside the cupboard under the TV. Place all edibles on the table. Put all CDs and books on the shelves. Put the pillows on the shelves as well. Put the trash bag in the trash pin.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Plug the xbox into the TV  | . Turn on the Xbox and the TV  | . Put the bowl of chips and bag of chips on the table |  Put the bowl of chips and bag of chips on the table . Put the xbox controller on table  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Plug the xbox into the TV. Turn on the Xbox and the TV. Put the bowl of chips and bag of chips on the table. Put the xbox controller on table. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Take the coffee from the microwave  | and place it on a counter  | . Plate  | a clean plate and put it next to the coffee mug  | . Take a hard boiled egg from the refrigerator  | and place it on the plate  | . Bring the prepared food  | and drink  | to me .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the coffee from the microwave and place it on a counter. Plate a clean plate and put it next to the coffee mug. Take a hard boiled egg from the refrigerator and place it on the plate. Bring the prepared food and drink to me.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Fill the mug with a drink from the freezer or water  | . Prepare the long cup with ramen and water  | using the ramen instructions and microwave  | . Bring the long cup  | prepared with ramen and a clean spoon and the mug  | to me .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the mug with a drink from the freezer or water. Prepare the long cup with ramen and water using the ramen instructions and microwave. Bring the long cup prepared with ramen and a clean spoon and the mug to me.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Set up the TV and the Xbox  | . Put the movie into the xbox  | . Place a pillow on each couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Set up the TV and the Xbox. Put the movie into the xbox. Place a pillow on each couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Find the videogame  | and put it inside the Xbox  | . Set up the Xbox with the TV  | . Put the drinks on the table with the bag of chips  | .
Arrange the couches so 3 are near the table with food a pillow on each .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Find the videogame and put it inside the Xbox. Set up the Xbox with the TV. Put the drinks on the table with the bag of chips.
Arrange the couches so 3 are near the table with food a pillow on each.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Set up the Xbox with the TV  | and put the music CD into the XBox  | . Put all books and other CDs on the shelve  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Set up the Xbox with the TV and put the music CD into the XBox. Put all books and other CDs on the shelve.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jd728@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Set up the TV  | with the Xbox turned  | on . Put a music CD into the Xbox  | and play  | . Put the bowl with chips on the table  | . Put all drinks and foods on the table  | . Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin |  Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin . Put all books and CDs on the group on shelves  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Set up the TV with the Xbox turned on. Put a music CD into the Xbox and play. Put the bowl with chips on the table. Put all drinks and foods on the table. Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin. Put all books and CDs on the group on shelves.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>837024146@qq.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>have some food  |  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : have some food </span> </sentence></point><point><email>837024146@qq.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Have  | some drink and food being  | served  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Have some drink and food being served</span> </sentence></point><point><email>837024146@qq.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>mix the ice cream into syrup  | .Take coffee  | slowly .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : mix the ice cream into syrup.Take coffee slowly</span> </sentence></point><point><email>837024146@qq.com</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>arrange all things in proper order  | .Eat the trash waste  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : arrange all things in proper order.Eat the trash waste.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>837024146@qq.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Boil the water  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Boil the water</span> </sentence></point><point><email>837024146@qq.com</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Stare at the empty dished  | .Arrange all the things  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Stare at the empty dished.Arrange all the things.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>837024146@qq.com</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Raise up the xbox  | .Prepare food and games in front of the arranged couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Raise up the xbox.Prepare food and games in front of the arranged couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>837024146@qq.com</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Prepare drinks and food  | .Serve the people  | when they come in .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Prepare drinks and food.Serve the people when they come in.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Take the pot  | and fill it with water  | . Put it in the microwave  | and start the microwave  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the pot and fill it with water. Put it in the microwave and start the microwave.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Grasp the brown book and math  | book . Toggle off the tv  | . Grasp the potato chips  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grasp the brown book and math book. Toggle off the tv. Grasp the potato chips.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>837024146@qq.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>cook and put the food on the bed  | .Put the pillows in good order  | .put on a DVD player  | .Set up a movie threater  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : cook and put the food on the bed.Put the pillows in good order.put on a DVD player.Set up a movie threater.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>grasp the cup, and syrup  | . open the fridge  | and grasp the ice cream  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp the cup, and syrup. open the fridge and grasp the ice cream.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>grasp the pot  | . Toggle the sink  | and fill the pot  | . Place pot on front left stove  | . Toggle front left stove  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp the pot. Toggle the sink and fill the pot. Place pot on front left stove. Toggle front left stove.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>grasp instant noodle  | . put water  | in pot  | . put pot on stove  | . put hot water in instant noodle  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp instant noodle. put water in pot. put pot on stove. put hot water in instant noodle.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>grasp movie, grasp  | chips grasp pillow .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp movie, grasp chips grasp pillow</span> </sentence></point><point><email>837024146@qq.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>play the movie  | .arrange various kinds of food  | .arrange pillows  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : play the movie.arrange various kinds of food.arrange pillows.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>grasp cd put in xbox  | . grasp bag of chips  | . grasp trash  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp cd put in xbox. grasp bag of chips. grasp trash.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>837024146@qq.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Get  | ramen cooked  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get ramen cooked.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>grasp plate  | 1 and plate 2 . Grasp long cup1, long cup2 and glass . Place  | plate1 and plate2 together and place the cups  | together .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp plate 1 and plate 2. Grasp long cup1, long cup2 and glass. Place plate1 and plate2 together and place the cups together.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>turn on tv,  | change  | to channel  | 1 . grasp bowl and pour into trash bin, grasp trash bag .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : turn on tv, change to channel 1. grasp bowl and pour into trash bin, grasp trash bag. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>grasp the pot,  | put it in the sink  | . open the faucet  | . grasp the pot  | and put it on the left stove  | . turn on the left stove  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp the pot, put it in the sink. open the faucet. grasp the pot and put it on the left stove. turn on the left stove.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>grasp the mug  | . grasp the spoon  | . place the mug on the table  | and scoop ice cream into the mug  | . then grasp syrup  | and squeeze the bottle  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp the mug. grasp the spoon. place the mug on the table and scoop ice cream into the mug. then grasp syrup and squeeze the bottle.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>grasp the remote turn on tv  | and turn  | to channel  | 3 . grasp chips  | and grasp pillow  | . drop at sofa  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp the remote turn on tv and turn to channel 3. grasp chips and grasp pillow. drop at sofa.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>grasp soda, | grasp chips, | grasp beer |. drop in trash can |. grasp trash bag  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp soda, grasp chips, grasp beer. drop in trash can. grasp trash bag. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>grasp book and drop on table  | . toggle tv  | off . grasp chips  | and drop on table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp book and drop on table. toggle tv off. grasp chips and drop on table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>grasp the trash bag  | and place it in the garbage bin  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp the trash bag and place it in the garbage bin. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>grasp far cry and xbox  | . drop near tv  | . grasp bowl and place on table . move couch near tv  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp far cry and xbox. drop near tv. grasp bowl and place on table. move couch near tv. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>grasp plate  | 1 and plate 2 and place in sink  | . grasp mug from inside the microwave  | and take it  | out .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp plate 1 and plate 2 and place in sink. grasp mug from inside the microwave and take it out.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>grasp the ramen  | . grasp the pot and place on back right stove  | . place the ramen in the pot  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp the ramen. grasp the pot and place on back right stove. place the ramen in the pot. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>grasp the two plates  | . place them in the sink  | . take the mug out of the microwave  | . shut the microwave door  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : grasp the two plates. place them in the sink. take the mug out of the microwave. shut the microwave door.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kl488@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>turn on tv  | and turn  | to channel  | 4 . grasp beer and coke  | and place on table  | and take trash  | and place it in the trash bin  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : turn on tv and turn to channel 4. grasp beer and coke and place on table and take trash and place it in the trash bin.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chenxiawu@cs.cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Grasp pot to the sink  | . Toggle tap  | to fill the pot with water  | . Grasp pot to the stove  | . Toggle the burner  | . Then grasp the instant ramen,  | open it  | and add seasoning  | . After the pot is boiling,  | pour the hot water to the cup of ramen  | .    .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grasp pot to the sink. Toggle tap to fill the pot with water. Grasp pot to the stove. Toggle the burner. Then grasp the instant ramen, open it and add seasoning. After the pot is boiling, pour the hot water to the cup of ramen.   </span> </sentence></point><point><email>chenxiawu@cs.cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn on the tv  | and set to movie channel  | . Turn up the volume  | . Arrange the pillow on the couch  | . Grasp the bear and the chips to the table in front of the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the tv and set to movie channel. Turn up the volume. Arrange the pillow on the couch. Grasp the bear and the chips to the table in front of the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chenxiawu@cs.cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on the TV  | and set to the music channel  | . Turn up the volume  | . Grasp the chips to the table in front of the couch  | . Arrange the couch to the corner  | to give more empty space in the middle of the room  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the TV and set to the music channel. Turn up the volume. Grasp the chips to the table in front of the couch. Arrange the couch to the corner to give more empty space in the middle of the room.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chenxiawu@cs.cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Grasp plate2 to the sink . Toggle the tap  | to wash  | plate2 . Put  | plate2 on plate1 and put them near the mug  | . Grasp  | glass1 and put it near the mug  | . Grasp chocolate syrup bottle and put it near the vanilla  | syrup bottle | syrup bottle .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grasp plate2 to the sink. Toggle the tap to wash plate2. Put plate2 on plate1 and put them near the mug. Grasp glass1 and put it near the mug. Grasp chocolate syrup bottle and put it near the vanilla syrup bottle. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>chenxiawu@cs.cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Turn off the TV  | . Grasp the brown book to the table in front of the couch  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off the TV. Grasp the brown book to the table in front of the couch. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>chenxiawu@cs.cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn on the TV  | and set to the movie channel  | . Arrange pillow1,pillow2,pillow3 on the couch . Grasp coke1 and beer1 to the table in front of the couch .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the TV and set to the movie channel. Arrange pillow1,pillow2,pillow3 on the couch. Grasp coke1 and beer1 to the table in front of the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put the game into the xbox  | . Get the food on the table  | for me . Pull out the coke on the table  | and rearrange them to the original place  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the game into the xbox. Get the food on the table for me. Pull out the coke on the table and rearrange them to the original place.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take out the coffee  | . Take out the ice cream and syrup on the table  | . Mix  | them together .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take out the coffee. Take out the ice cream and syrup on the table. Mix them together.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Get the bottle on the table in the kitchen  | . Fulfill it with water  | and then put it in the microwave oven until the temporature get 100 degree  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the bottle on the table in the kitchen. Fulfill it with water and then put it in the microwave oven until the temporature get 100 degree.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Prepare the drink  | by pouring the drink in the yellow bottle into an empty cup on the table  | . Prepare the food  | and take  | them to me .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Prepare the drink by pouring the drink in the yellow bottle into an empty cup on the table. Prepare the food and take them to me.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Take a movie from the CDs  | . Put it into the TV  | and play it  | . Prepare snacks . Get some pillows on the sofa  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take a movie from the CDs. Put it into the TV and play it. Prepare snacks. Get some pillows on the sofa. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Get out the movie  | and prepare for food in the fridge  | . take pillows  | and put it on the sofa  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get out the movie and prepare for food in the fridge. take pillows and put it on the sofa.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>get out ramen in the fridge  | and then put it on the plate  | . Add sauce  | and then mix it  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : get out ramen in the fridge and then put it on the plate. Add sauce and then mix it.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Get out the ramen from the fridge  | and then cook it in the pan  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get out the ramen from the fridge and then cook it in the pan.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Get the necessary books  | for me . Close the TV  | by clicking the button  | . Prepare food  | for me .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the necessary books for me. Close the TV by clicking the button. Prepare food for me.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Pick up one movie  | for me and play it  | . Get out chips form fridge  | . Get pillows  | for me .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up one movie for me and play it. Get out chips form fridge. Get pillows for me.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Pick up a game  | for me and play it in the xbox  | . Get some drink  | for me . After 10 minutes rearrange these to the original states  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up a game for me and play it in the xbox. Get some drink for me. After 10 minutes rearrange these to the original states.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Get some water in the cups  | and pour it in the pan  | . boil it for 5 minutes .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get some water in the cups and pour it in the pan. boil it for 5 minutes.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take out coffee, ice cream and syrup  | . Mix  | the together and pour it in a empty cup  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take out coffee, ice cream and syrup. Mix the together and pour it in a empty cup.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yl2254@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Get out drink and food for me from the fridge  | . Bring  | them to me by putting them in plates  | and bowls .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get out drink and food for me from the fridge. Bring them to me by putting them in plates and bowls.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>hema@cs.cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Take  | pot  | and fill water in it  | . Add ramen to the pot  | . place pot on stove,  | turn on the stove  | and let ramen cook for 5 min  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take pot and fill water in it. Add ramen to the pot. place pot on stove, turn on the stove and let ramen cook for 5 min. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>chenxiawu@cs.cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Grasp the kettle to the sink  | . Toggle the tap  | to fill the kettle  | . Put the kettle on the back-left burner of the stove  | . Toggle back-left burner  | . After the kettle is boiling,  | toggle off the back-left burner  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grasp the kettle to the sink. Toggle the tap to fill the kettle. Put the kettle on the back-left burner of the stove. Toggle back-left burner. After the kettle is boiling, toggle off the back-left burner. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>asheshjain399@gmail.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>get the bag of chips and bowl on the table  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : get the bag of chips and bowl on the table. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>asheshjain399@gmail.com</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>take the kettle to the sink  | and fill it with water  | . then place it on the stove  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : take the kettle to the sink and fill it with water. then place it on the stove</span> </sentence></point><point><email>asheshjain399@gmail.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>put bowl and cd's on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : put bowl and cd's on the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>asheshjain399@gmail.com</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>pick the beer bottle from the floor  | and throw it in the dustbin  | . also discard the content in the bowl  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : pick the beer bottle from the floor and throw it in the dustbin. also discard the content in the bowl.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>asheshjain399@gmail.com</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>put the bag of chips and books on the table  | . use the remote control on the table  | and turn off the tv  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : put the bag of chips and books on the table. use the remote control on the table and turn off the tv.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put xbox controller and game CD on the shelf  | . And remember  | to take care of the bear bottle and coke can  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put xbox controller and game CD on the shelf. And remember to take care of the bear bottle and coke can.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>There is music CD on the shelf . Drink some bear or coke  | if you want . And remember  | to take care of the trash  | though .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : There is music CD on the shelf. Drink some bear or coke if you want. And remember to take care of the trash though.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Let's play video game . You can find xbox right next to TV  | . Game CD is on the shelf . There is also coke and bear to drink and some potato chips . Sit on the couch  | to play  | though .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Let's play video game. You can find xbox right next to TV. Game CD is on the shelf. There is also coke and bear to drink and some potato chips. Sit on the couch to play though.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Use the kettle to boil water  | . You can get water  | by using the tab  | . Use stove to heat the kettle  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Use the kettle to boil water. You can get water by using the tab. Use stove to heat the kettle.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Can not boil water in this scenario  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Can not boil water in this scenario</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Let  | us play video game  | . Get the xbox and controller  | . We can have bear or coke while playing  | . Move the couch  | to face the TV  | so that we can sit on the couch  | to play  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Let us play video game. Get the xbox and controller. We can have bear or coke while playing. Move the couch to face the TV so that we can sit on the couch to play.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Can not find drink in this scenario  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Can not find drink in this scenario.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>No music CD found  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : No music CD found.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put the chip bag, cock and bear into the garbage bin  | . Put the xboxcontroller near TV remote  | . Take  | the garbageBag out of the room  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the chip bag, cock and bear into the garbage bin. Put the xboxcontroller near TV remote. Take the garbageBag out of the room.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Mix syrup and water to make a drink  | . You can get water  | by rotating the tab near sink  | . Use kettle to boil water  | and mix heated water with instantRamen  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Mix syrup and water to make a drink. You can get water by rotating the tab near sink. Use kettle to boil water and mix heated water with instantRamen.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Get the far cry game CD on the shelf  | and insert it into the xbox  | . xbox is right in front of the TV so there is no need to change its place  | . Food is already served on the table  | . No need to arrange couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the far cry game CD on the shelf and insert it into the xbox. xbox is right in front of the TV so there is no need to change its place. Food is already served on the table. No need to arrange couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Put water into the mug  | and use microwave  | to heat the mug  | . Then put the heated water into instantRamen  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put water into the mug and use microwave to heat the mug. Then put the heated water into instantRamen.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Get the kettle  | and put some water into it  | . Put the kettle on the stove  | and rotate the burner  | to heat the water  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the kettle and put some water into it. Put the kettle on the stove and rotate the burner to heat the water.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Get the far cry game CD on the desktop  | . No need to replace xbox  | . Put coke and bear near the potato chips  | . No need to re-arrange the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the far cry game CD on the desktop. No need to replace xbox. Put coke and bear near the potato chips. No need to re-arrange the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Clean all the plate . Then put Syrup into the fridge  | . All the cups and glass should be near to the kettle  | . After cleaning the plates,  | put them near the kettle  | too .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Clean all the plate. Then put Syrup into the fridge. All the cups and glass should be near to the kettle. After cleaning the plates, put them near the kettle too.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Put some water into the kettle  | and then use the stove  | to heat the kettle  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put some water into the kettle and then use the stove to heat the kettle.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Mix syrup with water  | to make a sweet drink  | . Use kettle and stove  | to boil some water  | . Mix the heated water with instantRamen .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Mix syrup with water to make a sweet drink. Use kettle and stove to boil some water. Mix the heated water with instantRamen.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Put some water into the kettle  | and use the stove  | to heat the kettle  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put some water into the kettle and use the stove to heat the kettle.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put xboxcontroller  | near xbox .| Put potato chips near coke  | . | Take trash bag outside of the room .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put xboxcontroller near xbox.| Put potato chips near coke. | Take trash bag outside of the room.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xx223@cornell.edu</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Put xbox near xbox controller | Put xbox near xbox controller .| Put bear near coke  | .| Take trash bag outside of the room .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put xbox near xbox controller.| Put bear near coke.| Take trash bag outside of the room.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>holomanga@gmail.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Find an object  | . If it is in the correct place, leave  | it . If it is in the incorrect place, pick  | it up and put it  | in the correct place . Repeat until all objects are in the correct place .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Find an object. If it is in the correct place, leave it. If it is in the incorrect place, pick it up and put it in the correct place. Repeat until all objects are in the correct place.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>d.j.parkes@staffs.ac.uk</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Look  | to see where things  | are dirty . Look  | to see where things are out of place,  | which need washing  | or putting  | away . Vacuum the carpet,  | straighten any cushions,  | pick up litter  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Look to see where things are dirty. Look to see where things are out of place, which need washing or putting away. Vacuum the carpet, straighten any cushions, pick up litter</span> </sentence></point><point><email>d.j.parkes@staffs.ac.uk</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Look  | to see where things  | are dirty . Look  | to see where things are out of place,  | which need washing  | or putting  | away . Vacuum the carpet,  | straighten any cushions,  | pick up litter  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Look to see where things are dirty. Look to see where things are out of place, which need washing or putting away. Vacuum the carpet, straighten any cushions, pick up litter</span> </sentence></point><point><email>sdk58@case.edu</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Please  | put these books on the bookshelf | put these books on the bookshelf . Turn the TV  | off . Clean that plate .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Please put these books on the bookshelf. Turn the TV off. Clean that plate.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>sdk58@case.edu</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Pour me some orange juice  | . Make pankcakes  | . I'll take a plate  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pour me some orange juice. Make pankcakes. I'll take a plate.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>eborochin@hotmail.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Clean the room .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Clean the room.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>inengland_2000@yahoo.com</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Take glass out of cupboard  | . Put orange juice in to the glass  | . Take bowl out of cupboard . Add corn flakes  | . Pour milk into bowl  | . Put glass and bowl on tray  | . Take tray to user  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take glass out of cupboard. Put orange juice in to the glass. Take bowl out of cupboard. Add corn flakes. Pour milk into bowl. Put glass and bowl on tray. Take tray to user. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>marknelson456@hotmail.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>fill the pot with water then boil the water in the pot on the stove | fill the pot with water then boil the water in the pot on the stove .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : fill the pot with water then boil the water in the pot on the stove.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dehix26@hotmail.fr</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Catch the pan,  | get to the fridge  | and fill water into it  | . Then go to the cockoven, toggle on a burner,  | place the filled  | pan on the toggled burner, wait it to boil to 100 degree C, toggle off the burner pan on the toggled burner, wait  | it to boil to 100 degree C, toggle off the burner  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Catch the pan, get to the fridge and fill water into it. Then go to the cockoven, toggle on a burner, place the filled pan on the toggled burner, wait it to boil to 100 degree C, toggle off the burner.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ajkey3@gmail.com</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Go grab the coffee, ice cream, and syrup .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Go grab the coffee, ice cream, and syrup.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ajkey3@gmail.com</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Go grab the ramen . Fill a pot  | with water put the pot on the stove  | then once the water is boiling  | add the ramen to the pot  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Go grab the ramen. Fill a pot with water put the pot on the stove then once the water is boiling add the ramen to the pot.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>1037103669@qq.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>care  | me .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : care me</span> </sentence></point><point><email>1037103669@qq.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>what i can do  | for you? .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : what i can do for you?</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mohamedaminejelassi@hotmail.com</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>prepare the ice cream  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : prepare the ice cream</span> </sentence></point><point><email>1037103669@qq.com</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>give me a cup of tea  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : give me a cup of tea</span> </sentence></point><point><email>1037103669@qq.com</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>open my car  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : open my car</span> </sentence></point><point><email>1037103669@qq.com</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>on
 .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : on
</span> </sentence></point><point><email>1037103669@qq.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Make Breakfast  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Make Breakfast</span> </sentence></point><point><email>1037103669@qq.com</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>turn on the music  | .give me some food  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : turn on the music.give me some food</span> </sentence></point><point><email>a.paladin95@gmail.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>j want to play tennis on pc  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : j want to play tennis on pc</span> </sentence></point><point><email>keturah.hetrick@gmail.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Put brown book on table  | . Pick up TV  | remote . Turn TV  | off . Open chips  | . Pour chips in bowl . Put bowl on table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put brown book on table. Pick up TV remote. Turn TV off. Open chips. Pour chips in bowl. Put bowl on table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>keturah.hetrick@gmail.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Fill kettle with water  | . Heat kettle on stove .
Pick  | up instantRamen1 . Pour instantRamen1 in mug . Pour water in kettle into mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill kettle with water. Heat kettle on stove.
Pick up instantRamen1. Pour instantRamen1 in mug. Pour water in kettle into mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>barasushi.knut@gmail.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Pick up the coffee, put a little bit of ice cream and syrup  | in it | in it .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the coffee, put a little bit of ice cream and syrup in it</span> </sentence></point><point><email>barasushi.knut@gmail.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Go  | get the books,  | turn off the tv  | and put out the food  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Go get the books, turn off the tv and put out the food</span> </sentence></point><point><email>barasushi.knut@gmail.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>get the ramen  | and cook it  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : get the ramen and cook it</span> </sentence></point><point><email>barasushi.knut@gmail.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>get the ramen  | and cook it  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : get the ramen and cook it</span> </sentence></point><point><email>schellenberg.marc@gmx.de</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>I am Hungry , I will make some breakfast  | . Do you also want something?
Lets  | make a Tea .
What about Cereals?
Would you like to eat on the table or on the couch? .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : I am Hungry , I will make some breakfast. Do you also want something?
Lets make a Tea.
What about Cereals?
Would you like to eat on the table or on the couch?</span> </sentence></point><point><email>info@bourree.de</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Get bottle  | and put it inside trash bin  | .
Get can  | and put it inside garbage bin  | .
Get Guiness Book  | and put it inside shelf  | .
Get brown book  |  and put it inside shelf  | .
Open bag of chips  | . and pour chips onto plate  | . 
Get  | pillow1_1 and put it onto seat_1
Get pillow1_2  | and put it onto seat_2
Get pillow1_3  | and put it  | onto seat_3


 .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get bottle and put it inside trash bin.
Get can and put it inside garbage bin.
Get Guiness Book and put it inside shelf.
Get brown book  and put it inside shelf.
Open bag of chips. and pour chips onto plate. 
Get pillow1_1 and put it onto seat_1
Get pillow1_2 and put it onto seat_2
Get pillow1_3 and put it onto seat_3


</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dirkjac@gmail.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Dave, take some coffee  | and then mix in ice cream and syrup  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Dave, take some coffee and then mix in ice cream and syrup.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dirkjac@gmail.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Dave, place the Xbox controller on the table,  | put the Cola can and the bottle into the trash | put the Cola can and the bottle into the trash .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Dave, place the Xbox controller on the table, put the Cola can and the bottle into the trash.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>konradmeier@gmail.com</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Set up the stereo  | . Connect it with a laptop  | . Make a playlist with popular 80s rock songs  | . Tidy up the room, so that things that can be broken are out of the way  | . Place some snacks on the table  | . Order pizza for when the party has started  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Set up the stereo. Connect it with a laptop. Make a playlist with popular 80s rock songs. Tidy up the room, so that things that can be broken are out of the way. Place some snacks on the table. Order pizza for when the party has started.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>konradmeier@gmail.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Arrange the couch in front of the tv  | . Put some snacks and drinks on the table  | . Make  | sure the xbox and the tv are connected  | . Place the controllers on the table  | . Check the dvd boxes  | if the right dvd is in the right box, and place all boxes on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Arrange the couch in front of the tv. Put some snacks and drinks on the table. Make sure the xbox and the tv are connected. Place the controllers on the table. Check the dvd boxes if the right dvd is in the right box, and place all boxes on the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>konradmeier@gmail.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Take all dirty dishes  | and put food leftovers in the trash  | . Put the dishes in the dishwasher  | and clean all surfaces with a sponge  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take all dirty dishes and put food leftovers in the trash. Put the dishes in the dishwasher and clean all surfaces with a sponge.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>konradmeier@gmail.com</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>arrange the couch so that xbox for the game night  | . check the games  | and xbox  | and make sure there is plenty of snacks and drinks  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : arrange the couch so that xbox for the game night. check the games and xbox and make sure there is plenty of snacks and drinks.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>konradmeier@gmail.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>clean the kitchen  | and make sure the dishes  | are empty before you put them in the dishwasher  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : clean the kitchen and make sure the dishes are empty before you put them in the dishwasher.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>konradmeier@gmail.com</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>make the room  | really cozy and place pillows and blankets in front of the tv and on the couch  | . give us a selection of romantic comedy  | and prepare  | some healthy snacks please  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : make the room really cozy and place pillows and blankets in front of the tv and on the couch. give us a selection of romantic comedy and prepare some healthy snacks please.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>konradmeier@gmail.com</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>clean  | and tidy up everything  | . put up some dark and evil gothic decorations  | and make sure we have loud death metal music  | . also, prepare some food that resembles gothic and vampire themes  | but is legal and yummy .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : clean and tidy up everything. put up some dark and evil gothic decorations and make sure we have loud death metal music. also, prepare some food that resembles gothic and vampire themes but is legal and yummy.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>konradmeier@gmail.com</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>put away all the dirty stuff in the kitchen  | and clean it  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : put away all the dirty stuff in the kitchen and clean it.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>konradmeier@gmail.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>put water in the boiler  | and turn it  | on .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : put water in the boiler and turn it on.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>konradmeier@gmail.com</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>first collect everything  | that comes to waste and trash it  | . Then clean the surfaces  | and tidy up the room  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : first collect everything that comes to waste and trash it. Then clean the surfaces and tidy up the room.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>konradmeier@gmail.com</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>place xbox games and food on a table in front of the couch  | . turn on the tv  | and learn  | how to play  | with us! .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : place xbox games and food on a table in front of the couch. turn on the tv and learn how to play with us!</span> </sentence></point><point><email>syxing@ucdavis.edu</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>turn on the music,  | put food on the table,  | clean up the room  |  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : turn on the music, put food on the table, clean up the room </span> </sentence></point><point><email>crawkn@gmail.com</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>put chairs in front of TV  | .  Put DVD in player  | .  Put pillows on chairs  | .  Put table between chairs and TV  | .  Put food and drinks on table  | .  Start movie .  lower lights  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : put chairs in front of TV.  Put DVD in player.  Put pillows on chairs.  Put table between chairs and TV.  Put food and drinks on table.  Start movie.  lower lights.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jtiger14@aim.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>turn off the tv,  | get some food  | and get the books to study  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : turn off the tv, get some food and get the books to study</span> </sentence></point><point><email>alan.agoldstein@gmail.com</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Get a put
Put ramen noodles in it
Place  | put on burner 
Turn burner  | on
Wait till water boils for 3 minutes
Turn burner  | off .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get a put
Put ramen noodles in it
Place put on burner 
Turn burner on
Wait till water boils for 3 minutes
Turn burner off</span> </sentence></point><point><email>alan.agoldstein@gmail.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Prepare coffee
Put in cup
Put in ice  | cream and syrup .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Prepare coffee
Put in cup
Put in ice cream and syrup</span> </sentence></point><point><email>alan.agoldstein@gmail.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Get eggs
Crack open in bowel
Discard shells
Mix eggs till yokes are broken
Place in frying pan
Cook under medium heat
Mix till eggs are solid 
Serve Get eggs
Crack open in bowel
Discard shells
Mix eggs till yokes are broken
Place  | in frying pan
Cook under medium heat
Mix  | till eggs are solid 
Serve .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get eggs
Crack open in bowel
Discard shells
Mix eggs till yokes are broken
Place in frying pan
Cook under medium heat
Mix till eggs are solid 
Serve</span> </sentence></point><point><email>seshu9@yahoo.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Get a pot,  | add water to the pot  | until almost full . Put the pot on the stove  | . Turn on the stove to medium high setting  | . Wait for water to boil  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get a pot, add water to the pot until almost full. Put the pot on the stove. Turn on the stove to medium high setting. Wait for water to boil.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>seshu9@yahoo.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Go to stereo or other music source  | . Play jazz music at a medium volume level  | . Move furniture such as chairs and tables closer to the walls so there is empty space in the center of the room  | . Get potato chips or peanuts or other snacks  | and place in bowls on the table  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Go to stereo or other music source. Play jazz music at a medium volume level. Move furniture such as chairs and tables closer to the walls so there is empty space in the center of the room. Get potato chips or peanuts or other snacks and place in bowls on the table. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>sbyeliab@gmail.com</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>find coffee  | and pour it into a bowl  | . Find ice cream  | and scooper and place one scoop of ice cream  | into bowl with scooper | into bowl with scooper . Find bottle of syrup  | and place it on top of ice cream in bowl  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : find coffee and pour it into a bowl. Find ice cream and scooper and place one scoop of ice cream into bowl with scooper. Find bottle of syrup and place it on top of ice cream in bowl.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>sbyeliab@gmail.com</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Find all school books in room and place on desk  | . Find soda and place on desk  | . Find chips and place in bowl  | . Place bowl with chips inside on desk . Find television  | remote and turn off television  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Find all school books in room and place on desk. Find soda and place on desk. Find chips and place in bowl. Place bowl with chips inside on desk. Find television remote and turn off television. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>sbyeliab@gmail.com</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Find CD and place in xbox  | . Play cd using xbox and tv  | . Find beer and soda  | and place them on desk  | . Find chips and bowl  | . Place chips in bowl and place bowl on desk . Move coffee table to side of room  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Find CD and place in xbox. Play cd using xbox and tv. Find beer and soda and place them on desk. Find chips and bowl. Place chips in bowl and place bowl on desk. Move coffee table to side of room.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>sbyeliab@gmail.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Boil water  | . Add egg  | and wait 12 minutes  | . Remove egg from water and place on plate  | . Make coffee  | and pour coffee into mug  | . Place Spoon, coffee, and plate together on table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Boil water. Add egg and wait 12 minutes. Remove egg from water and place on plate. Make coffee and pour coffee into mug. Place Spoon, coffee, and plate together on table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>sbyeliab@gmail.com</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Find kettle  | . Fill kettle 2/3 full with water  | . Place kettle on any stove burner  | . Turn stove burner with kettle on it  | on . Wait until water boils  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Find kettle. Fill kettle 2/3 full with water. Place kettle on any stove burner. Turn stove burner with kettle on it on. Wait until water boils.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>sethoroth999@yahoo.com</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>First find a food  | and make it  | . Popcorn is preferred  | when watching movies  | . After making food,  | bring the food within sight of the television  | . Next, insert the movie media into a playback device  | . Ensure that the device  | is connected  | and properly configured  | to show video on the screen  | . Start the video  | . Lastly, gather and arrange pillows around self  | until optimal temperature is obtained until optimal temperature is obtained  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : First find a food and make it. Popcorn is preferred when watching movies. After making food, bring the food within sight of the television. Next, insert the movie media into a playback device. Ensure that the device is connected and properly configured to show video on the screen. Start the video. Lastly, gather and arrange pillows around self until optimal temperature is obtained. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>cw659@cornell.com</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>put food on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : put food on the table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>rebecca.goro@gmail.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Go get me a bowl of chicken ramen .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Go get me a bowl of chicken ramen.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>leonariso@gmail.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Boil the water  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Boil the water</span> </sentence></point><point><email>digital_donna@msn.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Empty dishwasher
Put items in cupboard
clean countertop  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Empty dishwasher
Put items in cupboard
clean countertop</span> </sentence></point><point><email>digital_donna@msn.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Select xBox game
Turn on xBox
Take food from kitchen counter to game room table
Place couch 4 feet in front of television .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Select xBox game
Turn on xBox
Take food from kitchen counter to game room table
Place couch 4 feet in front of television</span> </sentence></point><point><email>digital_donna@msn.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>place movie in dvd player
put  | out favorite movie foods
put out extra pillows for couch and floor  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : place movie in dvd player
put out favorite movie foods
put out extra pillows for couch and floor</span> </sentence></point><point><email>digital_donna@msn.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>prepare coffee
place ice cream in tall glasses
pour coffee and syrup over ice cream .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : prepare coffee
place ice cream in tall glasses
pour coffee and syrup over ice cream</span> </sentence></point><point><email>editor@legacyhumans.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Mix a cup of coffee with a tablespoon of ice cream  | and then add just a bit of syrup  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Mix a cup of coffee with a tablespoon of ice cream and then add just a bit of syrup</span> </sentence></point><point><email>editor@legacyhumans.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Make a cup of coffee,  | then mix in a tablespoon of ice cream  | and then add a little syrup to the cup  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Make a cup of coffee, then mix in a tablespoon of ice cream and then add a little syrup to the cup.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>move.me@shaw.ca</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Make a pot of coffee  | . Toast 2 pieces of bread  | . Pour some coffee into a mug  | . Put the toasted bread on a plate  | . Bring the mug and the plate to the table  | . Bring cream, sugar and jam to the table  | . Bring cutlery and a napkin to the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Make a pot of coffee. Toast 2 pieces of bread. Pour some coffee into a mug. Put the toasted bread on a plate. Bring the mug and the plate to the table. Bring cream, sugar and jam to the table. Bring cutlery and a napkin to the table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>move.me@shaw.ca</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on the music  | . Move all furniture to the sides of the room  | . Put the food on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the music. Move all furniture to the sides of the room. Put the food on the table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>diepend@yahoo.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Pick things  | up, put  | them away, and throw away the trash  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick things up, put them away, and throw away the trash.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>diepend@yahoo.com</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Get music and food ready for the party  | . Clear the middle of the room  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get music and food ready for the party. Clear the middle of the room.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>diepend@yahoo.com</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Take dishes out of the dishwasher  | . Put  | them away .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take dishes out of the dishwasher. Put them away.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>diepend@yahoo.com</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Grab some xbox games  | and get the xbox  | ready .
Prepare  | some snacks
Move the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Grab some xbox games and get the xbox ready.
Prepare some snacks
Move the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>diepend@yahoo.com</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Boil water
Cook ramen  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Boil water
Cook ramen</span> </sentence></point><point><email>diepend@yahoo.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Get a drink  | out
Get the food ready
Serve breakfast  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get a drink out
Get the food ready
Serve breakfast</span> </sentence></point><point><email>diepend@yahoo.com</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Get textbooks  | ready
Turn off the TV
Grab snacks  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get textbooks ready
Turn off the TV
Grab snacks</span> </sentence></point><point><email>diepend@yahoo.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Bring all the textbooks
Turn off the TV
Bring food | Bring all the textbooks
Turn off the TV
Bring food .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Bring all the textbooks
Turn off the TV
Bring food</span> </sentence></point><point><email>diepend@yahoo.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Get drinks ready for everyone
Make breakfast
Put everything on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get drinks ready for everyone
Make breakfast
Put everything on the table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>diepend@yahoo.com</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Make  | coffee
Add ice cream and syrup  | to the coffee .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Make coffee
Add ice cream and syrup to the coffee</span> </sentence></point><point><email>diepend@yahoo.com</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Get some movies  | to choose from
Get lots of snacks
Bring pillows  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get some movies to choose from
Get lots of snacks
Bring pillows</span> </sentence></point><point><email>diepend@yahoo.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Get cups and drinks out
Make food for breakfast
Serve food for everyone | Get cups and drinks out
Make food for breakfast
Serve food for everyone .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get cups and drinks out
Make food for breakfast
Serve food for everyone</span> </sentence></point><point><email>diepend@yahoo.com</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Boil water
Add ramen noodles  | and cook  | until tender
Add contents  | of flavoring packet  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Boil water
Add ramen noodles and cook until tender
Add contents of flavoring packet</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jjm447@cornell.edu</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Pick  | up remote . Close TV  | . Move  | to counter  | . Pick up food  | . Bring it to Desk  | . Open books  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up remote. Close TV. Move to counter. Pick up food. Bring it to Desk. Open books. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>crazyromans@hotmail.com</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Get the cup of ramen,  | and add water to it  | . Then put the ramen in the microwave  | and cook it for a few minutes  | . Finally stir the ramen with a spoon  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the cup of ramen, and add water to it. Then put the ramen in the microwave and cook it for a few minutes. Finally stir the ramen with a spoon.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kumaran.ramanujam@gmail.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Cook me hot ramen  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Cook me hot ramen</span> </sentence></point><point><email>siddharth.gaur3@gmail.com</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>pick up the bowl
dump  | bowl contents in garbage bin
place cd on centre table
pick up beer 
drop beer near coke on centre table | bowl contents in garbage bin
place cd on centre table
pick up beer 
drop beer near coke on centre table .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : pick up the bowl
dump bowl contents in garbage bin
place cd on centre table
pick up beer 
drop beer near coke on centre table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>siddharth.gaur3@gmail.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>put ramen contents and 1 glass of water in kettle
put kettle on stove for 2 minutes
pour cooked ramen from kettle into plate put ramen contents and 1 glass of water in kettle
put kettle  | on stove for 2 minutes
pour cooked ramen from kettle into plate  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : put ramen contents and 1 glass of water in kettle
put kettle on stove for 2 minutes
pour cooked ramen from kettle into plate</span> </sentence></point><point><email>siddharth.gaur3@gmail.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>open fridge and have energydrink
empty instantramen and 1 longglass water into mug
put mug  | in microwave for 2 minutes
serve cooked instantramen from mug in Plate
 | in microwave for 2 minutes
serve cooked instantramen from mug in Plate
 .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : open fridge and have energydrink
empty instantramen and 1 longglass water into mug
put mug in microwave for 2 minutes
serve cooked instantramen from mug in Plate
</span> </sentence></point><point><email>siddharth.gaur3@gmail.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>pick up  cd from shelf and place on centre table
empty  | the bag of chips into bowl and place bowl on centre table
find pillows and arrange on couch the bag of chips into bowl and place bowl on centre table
find pillows and arrange on couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : pick up  cd from shelf and place on centre table
empty the bag of chips into bowl and place bowl on centre table
find pillows and arrange on couch</span> </sentence></point><point><email>jerry.weltman@gmail.com</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>make the bed
hang  | up clothes
pick up trash
  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : make the bed
hang up clothes
pick up trash
</span> </sentence></point><point><email>explosiveamphibians@gmail.com</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Put the cd on the table on the shelf close to the tv  | . Put all the books on the table  | . Put some food on the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the cd on the table on the shelf close to the tv. Put all the books on the table. Put some food on the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>explosiveamphibians@gmail.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Put a movie into the x box  | and bring some food to the table  | . Set some pillows on the couch  | too .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put a movie into the x box and bring some food to the table. Set some pillows on the couch too.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>xiaozhutouhuoguo@163.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take the coffee mug  | . Add ice-cream and chocolate syrup to the mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the coffee mug. Add ice-cream and chocolate syrup to the mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>First, you have to fill the kettle with water  | . Then, you put the kettle in the microwave and turn it  | on . Finally, wait  | until the water is boiling,  | and remove it from the microwave  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : First, you have to fill the kettle with water. Then, you put the kettle in the microwave and turn it on. Finally, wait until the water is boiling, and remove it from the microwave.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>First you have to pick up all the dishes  | and put them in the sink  | . Then, wash the dishes  | . Finally, collect them all into a neat stack  | . Then, you have to collect the silverware  | and put it next to the dishes  | . Finally, collect the cups  | and put them next to the silverware  | . Lastly, collect the other items  | and put them in their place (the ramen and the syrup)  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : First you have to pick up all the dishes and put them in the sink. Then, wash the dishes. Finally, collect them all into a neat stack. Then, you have to collect the silverware and put it next to the dishes. Finally, collect the cups and put them next to the silverware. Lastly, collect the other items and put them in their place (the ramen and the syrup).</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>First find the Shrek 2 movie  | and put it into the xbox  | . Next, the television has to be  | turned to the proper channel  | . Turn the xbox  | on to begin the movie  | . The food is prepared  | by pouring the chips into the bowl  | . Finally, grab the pillows from the shelf  | and arrange them on the chairs  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : First find the Shrek 2 movie and put it into the xbox. Next, the television has to be turned to the proper channel. Turn the xbox on to begin the movie. The food is prepared by pouring the chips into the bowl. Finally, grab the pillows from the shelf and arrange them on the chairs.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Fill the kettle with water,  | place it on the stove,  | then turn on the burner  | the kettle is on . When the water is done  | boiling,  | turn the burner  | off .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the kettle with water, place it on the stove, then turn on the burner the kettle is on. When the water is done boiling, turn the burner off.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Get the game  | and put it into the xbox  | . Hook the xbox up to the TV  | and turn it  | on . Pour the chips into the bowl,  | then take the bowl over to the table  | . Finally, put the pillow on the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the game and put it into the xbox. Hook the xbox up to the TV and turn it on. Pour the chips into the bowl, then take the bowl over to the table. Finally, put the pillow on the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Move the chairs back in front of  the TV  | . Pick up the random items that are on the floor  | and put them onto the table  | . Put the trash bag into the trash can |  Put the trash bag into the trash can .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Move the chairs back in front of  the TV. Pick up the random items that are on the floor and put them onto the table. Put the trash bag into the trash can. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Fill the kettle with water  | and put it on the stove burner  | . Turn the burner  | on . When the water has finished  | boiling,  | turn the burner  | off .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the kettle with water and put it on the stove burner. Turn the burner on. When the water has finished boiling, turn the burner off.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Pick up the glass  | and fill it with water,  | then set it down on the counter  | . Fill the kettle with water  | and place it on the stove  | . Boil the water,  | then put the ramen in the pot  | . When the ramen has finished  | cooking,  | pour the ramen out onto the plate  | . Place the plate near the glass  | . Finally, get some silverware  | and put it next to the plate  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the glass and fill it with water, then set it down on the counter. Fill the kettle with water and place it on the stove. Boil the water, then put the ramen in the pot. When the ramen has finished cooking, pour the ramen out onto the plate. Place the plate near the glass. Finally, get some silverware and put it next to the plate.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Find the game  | and put it into the xbox  | . Hook the xbox up to the television  | . Next, turn the television  | on . Open the bag of chips  | to have some food  | while you're playing  | . Finally, set the controller on the table near one of the chairs  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Find the game and put it into the xbox. Hook the xbox up to the television. Next, turn the television on. Open the bag of chips to have some food while you're playing. Finally, set the controller on the table near one of the chairs.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Get the coffee out of the microwave  | . The ice cream would be in the freezer,  | so get that out of the freezer  | and put a scoop on a plate  | . Add the syrup to the coffee  | and mix it with a spoon  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the coffee out of the microwave. The ice cream would be in the freezer, so get that out of the freezer and put a scoop on a plate. Add the syrup to the coffee and mix it with a spoon. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Put the movie disk into the xbox  | . Hook the xbox to the TV  | and make sure the TV is on the right channel  | . Fill the bowl with chips  | and put it on the table  | . Finally, put the pillow on the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the movie disk into the xbox. Hook the xbox to the TV and make sure the TV is on the right channel. Fill the bowl with chips and put it on the table. Finally, put the pillow on the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Fill the glass with water  | and place it on the serving area  | . Fill the instant ramen with water  | and heat it in the microwave  | . When the instant ramen is finished,  | put it on the serving area with a fork  | next to it .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill the glass with water and place it on the serving area. Fill the instant ramen with water and heat it in the microwave. When the instant ramen is finished, put it on the serving area with a fork next to it.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put the game disk into the xbox  | . Hook the xbox up to the TV  | and make sure the TV is on the right channel  | . Pour the chips into the bowl on the table  | . Finally, put the xbox controller on the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the game disk into the xbox. Hook the xbox up to the TV and make sure the TV is on the right channel. Pour the chips into the bowl on the table. Finally, put the xbox controller on the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>The game disk needs to go into the xbox  | . Next, hook the xbox to the TV  | and turn it  | on . Make  | sure the TV is tuned to the correct channel  | .  Open the bag of chips  | and put it on the table  | in front of the couch facing the TV  | . Finally, put the xbox controller  | on the couch facing the TV  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : The game disk needs to go into the xbox. Next, hook the xbox to the TV and turn it on. Make sure the TV is tuned to the correct channel.  Open the bag of chips and put it on the table in front of the couch facing the TV. Finally, put the xbox controller on the couch facing the TV.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>The glass has to be  | filled with water  | and put on the serving area  | . Then, the instant ramen gets some water in it as well . Heat the ramen in the microwave  | until it is done,  | then put it next to the glass on the serving area  | . Finally, place a fork near the instant ramen container  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : The glass has to be filled with water and put on the serving area. Then, the instant ramen gets some water in it as well. Heat the ramen in the microwave until it is done, then put it next to the glass on the serving area. Finally, place a fork near the instant ramen container.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Put the music disk in the xbox  | and connect it to the TV  | . Turn the TV to the appropriate channel for the xbox  | . Place the bowl of chips on the table near the couch  | . Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin |  Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin . Finally, put the pillows up on the shelf  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the music disk in the xbox and connect it to the TV. Turn the TV to the appropriate channel for the xbox. Place the bowl of chips on the table near the couch. Put the garbage bag into the garbage bin. Finally, put the pillows up on the shelf.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Find the game disk  | and put it into the xbox  | . Hook the xbox up to the TV  | and make sure the TV is on the proper channel  | .  Put the bowl of chips  | on the table near the couch facing the TV  | . Finally, put the xbox controller  | on the couch facing the TV  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Find the game disk and put it into the xbox. Hook the xbox up to the TV and make sure the TV is on the proper channel.  Put the bowl of chips on the table near the couch facing the TV. Finally, put the xbox controller on the couch facing the TV.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Put some water into the kettle  | . Then, heat the kettle on the stove burner  | until the water is burning  | . Finally, turn off the burner  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put some water into the kettle. Then, heat the kettle on the stove burner until the water is burning. Finally, turn off the burner.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Find the game disk  | and put it into the xbox  | . The xbox should be  | hooked up to the TV,  | and the TV should be  | tuned to the proper input channel  | . The chip bag should be  | emptied into the bowl,  | and the bowl will go onto the table  | near the couch facing the TV  | . Finally, the xbox controller will be  | placed  | on the couch facing the TV  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Find the game disk and put it into the xbox. The xbox should be hooked up to the TV, and the TV should be tuned to the proper input channel. The chip bag should be emptied into the bowl, and the bowl will go onto the table near the couch facing the TV. Finally, the xbox controller will be placed on the couch facing the TV.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ssm3tjololo@gmail.com</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put all of the dishes into the sink  | and wash  | them . Then, stack the dishes  | near the sink to dry  | . Next, do the same with the silverware,  | stacking them next to the dishes  | . Follow  | that by washing the cups/mugs/glasses/kettle, and put them near the other items to dry that by washing the cups/mugs/glasses/kettle, and put them near the other items  | to dry  | . Then, pick up the other items on the counter (salt, syrup, etc), and place them near the fridge on the counter  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all of the dishes into the sink and wash them. Then, stack the dishes near the sink to dry. Next, do the same with the silverware, stacking them next to the dishes. Follow that by washing the cups/mugs/glasses/kettle, and put them near the other items to dry. Then, pick up the other items on the counter (salt, syrup, etc), and place them near the fridge on the counter.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>libbybaldwin29@yahoo.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put the glass in the sink  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the glass in the sink.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>libbybaldwin29@yahoo.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put the mug in the sink  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put the mug in the sink. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>libbybaldwin29@yahoo.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Throw coke and beer in trash  | .
Put bag of chips in trash  | . 
Put Xbox remote on top of Xbox game |  
Put Xbox remote on top of Xbox game .
Arrange couches and chairs to face coffee table  | . 
Put book on shelf  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Throw coke and beer in trash.
Put bag of chips in trash. 
Put Xbox remote on top of Xbox game.
Arrange couches and chairs to face coffee table. 
Put book on shelf. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>cerawithac103@gmail.com</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>walk to the counter  | and double-click  | on "glass1" . Repeat for "plate1" . Carry items to sink and press E  | to put down the item in your right hand to put down the item in your right hand  | . Then press Q  | to put down the other item  | . Repeat for "spoon1" and "mug1" . Walk to the corner of the room to the right of the sink and double-click on "plate1" on the floor  | . Take item  | to sink and press E  | to put down to put  | down .   .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : walk to the counter and double-click on "glass1". Repeat for "plate1". Carry items to sink and press E to put down the item in your right hand. Then press Q to put down the other item. Repeat for "spoon1" and "mug1". Walk to the corner of the room to the right of the sink and double-click on "plate1" on the floor. Take item to sink and press E to put down.  </span> </sentence></point><point><email>buckzmusic93@gmail.com</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>pickup books place on shelf,  | turn  | on then turn off the tv  | and pick up food  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : pickup books place on shelf, turn on then turn off the tv and pick up food.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>buckzmusic93@gmail.com</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>pick up empty dishes and pickup and put away things pick up empty dishes and pickup and put away things  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : pick up empty dishes and pickup and put away things</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take your coffee  | . Grab the ice cream  | and put it inside the coffee  | . Put the ice cream  | back and take the syrup  | . Pour the syrup inside the coffee  | and put the syrup  | away .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take your coffee. Grab the ice cream and put it inside the coffee. Put the ice cream back and take the syrup. Pour the syrup inside the coffee and put the syrup away.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Take the DVD  | and put it inside the DVD player  | . Take the pillows from your bed  | and move them to the couch  | . Take the popcorn  | and put it in the microwave  | . Move the popped popcorn to the coffee table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the DVD and put it inside the DVD player. Take the pillows from your bed and move them to the couch. Take the popcorn and put it in the microwave. Move the popped popcorn to the coffee table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Take the pot to the sink  | . Fill the pot with water  | . Move the pot to the stove  | . Turn the stove  | on .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the pot to the sink. Fill the pot with water. Move the pot to the stove. Turn the stove on.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Take the pot  | and move it to the sink  | . Fill the pot with water  | . Move the pot to the stove  | . Turn the stove  | on .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the pot and move it to the sink. Fill the pot with water. Move the pot to the stove. Turn the stove on.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Take the game  | and put it inside the Xbox  | . Move chairs in front of the TV in a row  | .  Take bag of chips  | and move it beside the TV  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the game and put it inside the Xbox. Move chairs in front of the TV in a row.  Take bag of chips and move it beside the TV.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Turn on the kettle  | . Pick up the instant ramen  | . Put it inside a pot  | . Pour the water from the kettle  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the kettle. Pick up the instant ramen. Put it inside a pot. Pour the water from the kettle.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on music  | . Put the Xbox on the shelf  | . Take the pack of chips  | and put it on the table  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on music. Put the Xbox on the shelf. Take the pack of chips and put it on the table. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Turn on the kettle  | . Pour the kettle into the ramen  | . Take a fork  | to eat the ramen  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the kettle. Pour the kettle into the ramen. Take a fork to eat the ramen.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Move the couch  | to be  | facing the TV  | .  Take the chips  | and put them by the couch  | . Take the pillow from the shelf  | and put it on the couch  | . Put the CD by the television  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Move the couch to be facing the TV.  Take the chips and put them by the couch. Take the pillow from the shelf and put it on the couch. Put the CD by the television.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Take the kettle  | and fill it with water  | . Put the kettle on the stove  | and turn the stove  | on .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the kettle and fill it with water. Put the kettle on the stove and turn the stove on.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on the television  | . Move the bag of chips to the bowl  | . Move the garbage bag to the trash  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on the television. Move the bag of chips to the bowl. Move the garbage bag to the trash.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Pick up plates and cups  | and put them in the sink  | . Pick up the kettle, instant ramen, chocolate syrup, and energy drink  | and place them all beside each other on the counter  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up plates and cups and put them in the sink. Pick up the kettle, instant ramen, chocolate syrup, and energy drink and place them all beside each other on the counter.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Pick up the coke, beer, and bowl  | and place them all beside each other on the table  | . Pick up the garbage bag  | and move it to the garbage bin  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the coke, beer, and bowl and place them all beside each other on the table. Pick up the garbage bag and move it to the garbage bin.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Move pillows from the shelf  | and put them on the couch  | . Move the CD to the television  | . Eat the bag of chips  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Move pillows from the shelf and put them on the couch. Move the CD to the television. Eat the bag of chips.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Move the books to the table  | . Turn off the television  | . Move the bowl to the table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Move the books to the table. Turn off the television. Move the bowl to the table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Move the CD to the XBox  | . Move the couch to in front of the television  | . Take the bag of chips  | and move them to the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Move the CD to the XBox. Move the couch to in front of the television. Take the bag of chips and move them to the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Take the kettle  | and move it to the stove  | . Take the ramen  | and put it inside the kettle  | . Turn on the stove  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the kettle and move it to the stove. Take the ramen and put it inside the kettle. Turn on the stove.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Move the garbage bag to the garbage bin | Move the garbage bag to the garbage bin . Turn off the television  | . Pick up the book  | and move it to the shelf  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Move the garbage bag to the garbage bin. Turn off the television. Pick up the book and move it to the shelf.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Move the kettle to the stove  | . Turn on the stove  | . Put the ramen inside the kettle  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Move the kettle to the stove. Turn on the stove. Put the ramen inside the kettle.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>will.boffa@gmail.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Take the kettle  | and move it to the stove  | . Put the ramen inside the kettle  | . Turn on the stove  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the kettle and move it to the stove. Put the ramen inside the kettle. Turn on the stove.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>janedoexyz123@outlook.com</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Get coke and boiled egg out of the fridge  | . Serve it  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get coke and boiled egg out of the fridge. Serve it.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>janedoexyz123@outlook.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Get the mug  | and heat up coffee in the microwave  | . Get the ice cream out of the fridge  | . Scoop ice cream into a bowl  | . Pour coffee into the bowl  | . Add syrup to the bowl  | . Put ice cream back into the fridge  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get the mug and heat up coffee in the microwave. Get the ice cream out of the fridge. Scoop ice cream into a bowl. Pour coffee into the bowl. Add syrup to the bowl. Put ice cream back into the fridge.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yejz77@gmail.com</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>make food,  | get pillows,  | watch movie  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : make food, get pillows, watch movie</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yejz77@gmail.com</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>arrange things and take out trash waste then sit on the chair  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : arrange things and take out trash waste then sit on the chair</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yejz77@gmail.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Go to the game system  | and go to the xbox,  | get the food  | and arrange couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Go to the game system and go to the xbox, get the food and arrange couch</span> </sentence></point><point><email>beautifuldolphins47@yahoo.com</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Pick up books off of the floor  | . Place books on desk  | .
Walk up to the remote on counter . Turn tv  | off .
Pick up the beer bottle off the floor  | . Place bottle on the counter  | .

 .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up books off of the floor. Place books on desk.
Walk up to the remote on counter. Turn tv off.
Pick up the beer bottle off the floor. Place bottle on the counter.

</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yejz77@gmail.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Take coffee,  | eat the ice cream  | and use syrup for ice cream  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take coffee, eat the ice cream and use syrup for ice cream</span> </sentence></point><point><email>beautifuldolphins47@yahoo.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Turn off water faucet in kitchen  | .
Pick up cup on the counter  | . Pour water out of cup  | .
Pick up chocolate syrup  | . Walk to fridge  | . Open fridge . Put chocolate syrup into the fridge  | . Close the fridge  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off water faucet in kitchen.
Pick up cup on the counter. Pour water out of cup.
Pick up chocolate syrup. Walk to fridge. Open fridge. Put chocolate syrup into the fridge. Close the fridge.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>beautifuldolphins47@yahoo.com</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Pick up CD  | . Insert CD into xbox  | . Put down xbox  | .
Pick up coke can  | . Put can down on the center table  | .
Move the pillows to ends of the couch  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up CD. Insert CD into xbox. Put down xbox.
Pick up coke can. Put can down on the center table.
Move the pillows to ends of the couch.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>caliboy1234@hotmail.com</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Pick up the kettle  | . Go  | fill it with water from the sink  | . Go to the stove  | . Place the kettle on the right front burner  | .  Open the front right burner  | . Wait  | until it boils .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the kettle. Go fill it with water from the sink. Go to the stove. Place the kettle on the right front burner.  Open the front right burner. Wait until it boils. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>caliboy1234@hotmail.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Go to the sofa  | . Pick up the xbox controller  | and place it on the xbox  | . Go to the TV  | and turn it  | off . Go to the coffee table  | and pick up the book  | . Go to the sofa  | and place the book  | down . Go over to the long tables  | . Pick up chips,  | bring them to the sofa  | and place them next to the book  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Go to the sofa. Pick up the xbox controller and place it on the xbox. Go to the TV and turn it off. Go to the coffee table and pick up the book. Go to the sofa and place the book down. Go over to the long tables. Pick up chips, bring them to the sofa and place them next to the book. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>barrieautumn23@yahoo.com</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Empty all dishes into the sink  | .
Arrange all condiments and food items on counter  | .
Wipe fridge with cloth .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Empty all dishes into the sink.
Arrange all condiments and food items on counter.
Wipe fridge with cloth.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>barrieautumn23@yahoo.com</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Gather all used cups and glasses and place into the sink  | . Gather  | and arrange Ramen, vanilla syrup, and chocolate syrup on the counter | and arrange Ramen, vanilla syrup, and chocolate syrup on the counter . Wipe the counter with a cloth  | . Wipe fridge door .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Gather all used cups and glasses and place into the sink. Gather and arrange Ramen, vanilla syrup, and chocolate syrup on the counter. Wipe the counter with a cloth. Wipe fridge door.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>barrieautumn23@yahoo.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Pick up LongCup  | and pour liquid down the sink  | . Put LongCup in the sink  | . Pick up Mug1  | and empty liquid into the sink  | . Put Mug1 into the sink  | . Pick up salt  | and place it next to the Ramen noodles  | . Pick up vanilla syrup  | and place it next to the Ramen  | . Pick up chocolate syrup  | and place it next to the Vanilla syrup  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up LongCup and pour liquid down the sink. Put LongCup in the sink. Pick up Mug1 and empty liquid into the sink. Put Mug1 into the sink. Pick up salt and place it next to the Ramen noodles. Pick up vanilla syrup and place it next to the Ramen. Pick up chocolate syrup and place it next to the Vanilla syrup. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>barrieautumn23@yahoo.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Fill kettle with hot water from the sink  | . Place the kettle on the stove  | . Turn on the burner for the kettle  | . Once the water boils, turn off stove burner  | . Pour kettle water into instant Ramen  | . Pick up spoon  | and stir Ramen  | . Pick up mug  | and fill halfway with water  | . Add chocolate syrup to mug  | . Serve the Ramen, spoon, and mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill kettle with hot water from the sink. Place the kettle on the stove. Turn on the burner for the kettle. Once the water boils, turn off stove burner. Pour kettle water into instant Ramen. Pick up spoon and stir Ramen. Pick up mug and fill halfway with water. Add chocolate syrup to mug. Serve the Ramen, spoon, and mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>barrieautumn23@yahoo.com</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Pick up the x-box controller place it on the Xbox  | . Pick up TV  | remote and turn the station to a music channel  | . Put the bowl on the table  | and fill the bowl with chips  | . Put the coke can onto the table  | . Put the beer bottle on the table  | . Take garbage bag  | and throw it  | away .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the x-box controller place it on the Xbox. Pick up TV remote and turn the station to a music channel. Put the bowl on the table and fill the bowl with chips. Put the coke can onto the table. Put the beer bottle on the table. Take garbage bag and throw it away.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yoanrodriguez24@gmail.com</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>pick up books  | and move to table
turn off tv
gather food  | and put on table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : pick up books and move to table
turn off tv
gather food and put on table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>yoanrodriguez24@gmail.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Tell  | Me Dave website has been  | visited 5000 times  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Tell Me Dave website has been visited 5000 times</span> </sentence></point><point><email>ammturk@hotmail.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Turn off the TV  | .
Pick up brown book  | .
Put brown book on table  | .
Pick up bowl  | .
Put bowl on table  | .
Pick up beer  | .
Put beer on table  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off the TV.
Pick up brown book.
Put brown book on table.
Pick up bowl.
Put bowl on table.
Pick up beer.
Put beer on table.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>darthtux@gmail.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Pick up trash bag  | .
Put trash bag in garbage bin  | .
Pick up Guiness Book  | .
Put Guiness Book on coffee table  | .
Pick up bag of chips  | .
Put bag of chips in garbage bin  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up trash bag.
Put trash bag in garbage bin.
Pick up Guiness Book.
Put Guiness Book on coffee table.
Pick up bag of chips.
Put bag of chips in garbage bin.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>mgnhrt1@gmail.com</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Put ice cream in the fridge  | - Put away fork and spoon  | - Put away salt  | - Put away vanilla syrup  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put ice cream in the fridge - Put away fork and spoon - Put away salt - Put away vanilla syrup</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kelley.parker07@gmail.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Pick up coke  | and put it on the table  | .  Pick up the controller  | and put it on the table  | .  Pick up the beer bottle  | and put it on the table  | .  Put the trash waste in the garbage bin  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up coke and put it on the table.  Pick up the controller and put it on the table.  Pick up the beer bottle and put it on the table.  Put the trash waste in the garbage bin.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>kelley.parker07@gmail.com</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Take the items out of the refrigerator and freezer  | and put them on the counter  | .   Put the kettle on the oven burner  | and begin  | cooking the ramen  | .  Drink the coke  | and eat the ramen  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Take the items out of the refrigerator and freezer and put them on the counter.   Put the kettle on the oven burner and begin cooking the ramen.  Drink the coke and eat the ramen. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>aschwietert@gmail.com</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Get  | a pot
add  | desired amount  | of water
put on the stove
turn  | the stove on
the water is done  | when a bunch of  bubbles are rising from the bottom of the pot  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Get a pot
add desired amount of water
put on the stove
turn the stove on
the water is done when a bunch of  bubbles are rising from the bottom of the pot</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on music  | .
Pick up video game controller  | . Place on table  | .
Pick up Ramen  | . Put in microwave  | . Turn on microwave  | . Remove Ramen from microwave  | .
 .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on music.
Pick up video game controller. Place on table.
Pick up Ramen. Put in microwave. Turn on microwave. Remove Ramen from microwave.
</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Remove coffee mug from microwave  | .
Pick up ice cream  | .
Add ice cream to mug  | .
Pick up syrup  | .
Add syrup to mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Remove coffee mug from microwave.
Pick up ice cream.
Add ice cream to mug.
Pick up syrup.
Add syrup to mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on music  | .
Pick up video game controller  | .
Place controller on table,
Pick  | of Ramen | of Ramen .
Put in microwave  | .
Turn microwave  | on .
Remove Ramen from microwave  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on music.
Pick up video game controller.
Place controller on table,
Pick of Ramen.
Put in microwave.
Turn microwave on.
Remove Ramen from microwave.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Pick up Canada Dry  | . 
Pick up Instant Ramen  | . Put in microwave  | . Turn microwave  | on . Remove Instant Ramen  | .
Serve Canada Dry . Serve Instant Ramen .

 .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up Canada Dry. 
Pick up Instant Ramen. Put in microwave. Turn microwave on. Remove Instant Ramen.
Serve Canada Dry. Serve Instant Ramen.

</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Pick up bag of chips  | . Discard bag of chips in garbage .
Pick up soda  | . Discard soda in garbage .
Pick up garbage  | . Discard garbage  | .
Pick up book  | . Place book on shelf  | .
Pick up bottle  | . Place bottle on shelf  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up bag of chips. Discard bag of chips in garbage.
Pick up soda. Discard soda in garbage.
Pick up garbage. Discard garbage.
Pick up book. Place book on shelf.
Pick up bottle. Place bottle on shelf. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Turn on Television  | . 
Pick up XBox  | .
Turn on XBox  | .
Put XBox on shelf  | .
Pick up Instant Ramen  | .
Put Instant Ramen in microwave  | .
Turn on microwave  | .
Remove Instant Ramen  | .
Pick up couch  | .
Move couch two feet closer to television  | .
Sit on couch  | .
Pick up XBox controller  | .
Play game on XBox  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on Television. 
Pick up XBox.
Turn on XBox.
Put XBox on shelf.
Pick up Instant Ramen.
Put Instant Ramen in microwave.
Turn on microwave.
Remove Instant Ramen.
Pick up couch.
Move couch two feet closer to television.
Sit on couch.
Pick up XBox controller.
Play game on XBox.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Pick up coffee mug  | .
Pick up ice cream  | .
Put ice cream in coffee mug  | .
Pick up syrup  | .
Put syrup in coffee mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up coffee mug.
Pick up ice cream.
Put ice cream in coffee mug.
Pick up syrup.
Put syrup in coffee mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Pick up Long cup  | .
Walk to faucet  | .
Turn on faucet  | .
Fill Long cup with water from faucet  | .
Pour water into pot  | .
Put pot on right front stove burner  | .
Turn right front burner  | on .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up Long cup.
Walk to faucet.
Turn on faucet.
Fill Long cup with water from faucet.
Pour water into pot.
Put pot on right front stove burner.
Turn right front burner on.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Pick up book  | . Put book on shelf  | . 
Pick up XBox  | . Put XBox on shelf  | . 
Pick up television  | remote . Put television remote on shelf  | .
Pick up bag of chips  | . Put bag of chips in the garbage  | bag .
Pick up garbage bag  | . Discard garbage bag  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up book. Put book on shelf. 
Pick up XBox. Put XBox on shelf. 
Pick up television remote. Put television remote on shelf.
Pick up bag of chips. Put bag of chips in the garbage bag.
Pick up garbage bag. Discard garbage bag.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Pick up Instant Ramen  | . Put into microwave  | . Turn microwave  | on . Serve Ramen .
Pick up coffee mug  | . Serve coffee  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up Instant Ramen. Put into microwave. Turn microwave on. Serve Ramen.
Pick up coffee mug. Serve coffee.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Pick up coffee mug  | .
Pick up ice cream  | .
Put ice cream in coffee mug  | .
Pick up syrup  | .
Put syrup in coffee mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up coffee mug.
Pick up ice cream.
Put ice cream in coffee mug.
Pick up syrup.
Put syrup in coffee mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Pick up coffee mug  | .
Pick up ice cream  | .
Put ice cream in coffee mug  | .
Pick up syrup  | .
Put syrup in coffee mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up coffee mug.
Pick up ice cream.
Put ice cream in coffee mug.
Pick up syrup.
Put syrup in coffee mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Pick up dishes  | .
Put dishes in  sink  | .
Pick up book  | . Put book on shelf  | .
Pick up XBox  | . Put XBox on shelf  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up dishes.
Put dishes in  sink.
Pick up book. Put book on shelf.
Pick up XBox. Put XBox on shelf.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn on television  | . Pick up television  | remote . Press pay-per-view button  | on remote .
Pick up Instant Ramen  | . Put Instant Ramen in microwave  | . Turn on microwave  | . Put instant Ramen on coffee table  | .
Pick up pillows  | . Put pillows on couch  | .
Sit on couch  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on television. Pick up television remote. Press pay-per-view button on remote.
Pick up Instant Ramen. Put Instant Ramen in microwave. Turn on microwave. Put instant Ramen on coffee table.
Pick up pillows. Put pillows on couch.
Sit on couch. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Pick up coffee mug  | .
Pick up ice cream  | .
Put ice cream in coffee mug  | .
Pick up syrup  | .
Put syrup in coffee mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up coffee mug.
Pick up ice cream.
Put ice cream in coffee mug.
Pick up syrup.
Put syrup in coffee mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on radio  | .
Pick up Instant Ramen  | . Put Instant Ramen in microwave  | . Turn on microwave  | . Remove Instant Ramen  | .  Put Instant Ramen on counter  | .
Pick up garbage bag  | . Discard garbage bag  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on radio.
Pick up Instant Ramen. Put Instant Ramen in microwave. Turn on microwave. Remove Instant Ramen.  Put Instant Ramen on counter.
Pick up garbage bag. Discard garbage bag.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Pick up coffee mug  | .
Pick up ice cream  | .
Put ice cream in coffee mug  | .
Pick up syrup  | .
Put syrup in coffee mug  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up coffee mug.
Pick up ice cream.
Put ice cream in coffee mug.
Pick up syrup.
Put syrup in coffee mug.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Pick up book  | . Put book on shelf  | .
Pick up television  | remote . Press the off button  | on the remote .
Pick up Instant Ramen  | . Put Instant Ramen in microwave  | . Turn on microwave  | . Remove Instant Ramen  | . Put Instant Ramen on counter  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up book. Put book on shelf.
Pick up television remote. Press the off button on the remote.
Pick up Instant Ramen. Put Instant Ramen in microwave. Turn on microwave. Remove Instant Ramen. Put Instant Ramen on counter.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Turn on radio  | .
Pick up Instant Ramen  | . Put Instant Ramen in microwave  | . Turn on microwave  | . Remove Instant Ramen  | . Put Instant Ramen on counter  | .
Pick up garbage bag  | . Discard garbage bag  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on radio.
Pick up Instant Ramen. Put Instant Ramen in microwave. Turn on microwave. Remove Instant Ramen. Put Instant Ramen on counter.
Pick up garbage bag. Discard garbage bag.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>malibu78321@yahoo.com</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Pick up book  | . Put book on shelf  | . 
Pick up television  | remote . Press the off button on television remote  | .
Pick up Instant Ramen  | . Put Instant Ramen in microwave  | . Turn microwave  | on . Remove Instant Ramen  | . Put Instant Ramen on counter  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up book. Put book on shelf. 
Pick up television remote. Press the off button on television remote.
Pick up Instant Ramen. Put Instant Ramen in microwave. Turn microwave on. Remove Instant Ramen. Put Instant Ramen on counter.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Serve milk in a glass  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Serve milk in a glass.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Put water in the mug  | and hit in the microwave for three minutes  | . Take a tea bag  | and left for 3 min  | and serve  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put water in the mug and hit in the microwave for three minutes. Take a tea bag and left for 3 min and serve.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Fill cup with cereal  | . Then, take the syrup  | and squeeze over the cereal  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill cup with cereal. Then, take the syrup and squeeze over the cereal.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn of TV  | and select movie in Neflix  | . Put popcorn bag in the microwave for 3 min  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn of TV and select movie in Neflix. Put popcorn bag in the microwave for 3 min.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Turn off TV  | and put book 2 over the table  | . Open the bag of chips  | and put in a bowl  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off TV and put book 2 over the table. Open the bag of chips and put in a bowl.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn on TV  | and put chips in a bowl  | .  .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on TV and put chips in a bowl. </span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Open the refrigerator  | and take three spoons of ice cream in a cup  | . Take syrup and squeeze over the ice cream  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Open the refrigerator and take three spoons of ice cream in a cup. Take syrup and squeeze over the ice cream.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>2</objective><sentence>Add three scoops of ice cream in the bowl,  | add a half cup of coffee  | . Put syrup on top  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Add three scoops of ice cream in the bowl, add a half cup of coffee. Put syrup on top.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Clean dishes and pick-up things from counter .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Clean dishes and pick-up things from counter.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Turn off TV and put books over the center table  | .  Put pop corn in the microwave  | and serve  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off TV and put books over the center table.  Put pop corn in the microwave and serve.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Arrange pillows over the couch  | . Turn on xbox  | and serve coca-cola  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Arrange pillows over the couch. Turn on xbox and serve coca-cola.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Pour water in the cup and boil in the microwave  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pour water in the cup and boil in the microwave.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>5</objective><sentence>Put milk in a glass  | and add vanilla syrup  | . Serve  | hot .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put milk in a glass and add vanilla syrup. Serve hot.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Put all ramen in the kettle  | . Add four cups of water  | and put in the stove for 10 min  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put all ramen in the kettle. Add four cups of water and put in the stove for 10 min.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Turn off TV and put pillows in the couch  | . Put books over the table  | and serve chips in a bowl  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn off TV and put pillows in the couch. Put books over the table and serve chips in a bowl.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Put pillows over the couches  | . Turn on xbox  | and serve beer, coca-cola and chips  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put pillows over the couches. Turn on xbox and serve beer, coca-cola and chips.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Pull table  | aside . Turn on radio  | and put chips in a bowl  | . Serve beer and soda  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pull table aside. Turn on radio and put chips in a bowl. Serve beer and soda.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Put pillows oven the center couch  |  . Put the chips in the bowl  | and turn on TV  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put pillows oven the center couch . Put the chips in the bowl and turn on TV.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Fill cup with water and boil in the microwave  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Fill cup with water and boil in the microwave.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>dolita52@mail.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>Put chips in a bowl  | and put music  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Put chips in a bowl and put music.</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>10</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Pick up pot
Turn on sink
Fill pot
Turn off sink
Set on stove
Turn on stove
Turn off stove Pick up pot
Turn on sink
Fill pot
Turn  | off sink
Set on stove
Turn on stove
Turn off stove .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up pot
Turn on sink
Fill pot
Turn off sink
Set on stove
Turn on stove
Turn off stove</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>2</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Pick up kettle
Goto Fridge
Open water dispenser
Close water  | dispenser
Goto Stove
Place down kettle
Open back left burner  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up kettle
Goto Fridge
Open water dispenser
Close water dispenser
Goto Stove
Place down kettle
Open back left burner</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>9</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Pick up ramen
Put  | down ramen
Pick up plate
Put  | down plate
Open fridge
 down plate
Open fridge
 | down plate
Open fridge
 .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up ramen
Put down ramen
Pick up plate
Put down plate
Open fridge
</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>12</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Pick up trash
Pick up remote 1
Pick up controller 1
Pick up cd
pick up Xbox
Put down cd
Put down object
 Pick  | up trash
Pick  | up remote 1
Pick up controller 1
Pick  | up cd
pick up Xbox
Put down cd
Put down object
 | up cd
pick up Xbox
Put down cd
Put down object
 .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up trash
Pick up remote 1
Pick up controller 1
Pick up cd
pick up Xbox
Put down cd
Put down object
</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>18</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Pick up boot
Place book on table
Turn off the TV
Pick up chips and bowl
Place chips and bowl on table Pick up boot
Place book on table
Turn off the TV
Pick up chips and bowl
Place chips and bowl on table | Pick up boot
Place book on table
Turn off the TV
Pick up chips and bowl
Place chips and bowl on table .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up boot
Place book on table
Turn off the TV
Pick up chips and bowl
Place chips and bowl on table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>3</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Pick up the kettle
fill with water from fridge
place on back right burner
turn  | back right burner on .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the kettle
fill with water from fridge
place on back right burner
turn back right burner on</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>14</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>pick up beer
place beer on table
turn on tv
pick up bowl
dump bowl in trash
 | pick up beer
place beer on table
turn on tv
pick up bowl
dump bowl in trash
 .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : pick up beer
place beer on table
turn on tv
pick up bowl
dump bowl in trash
</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>8</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>pick up ramen
fill with water from fridge
place ramen in microwave | pick up ramen
fill with water from fridge
place ramen in microwave .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : pick up ramen
fill with water from fridge
place ramen in microwave</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>5</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>pick up kettle
fill with water from fridge
place kettle on stove
turn burner on | pick up kettle
fill with water from fridge
place kettle on stove
turn burner on .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : pick up kettle
fill with water from fridge
place kettle on stove
turn burner on</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>4</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Pick up ramen
fill with water from fridge
place ramen  | in microwave
turn the microwave on .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up ramen
fill with water from fridge
place ramen in microwave
turn the microwave on</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>1</scenario><objective>4</objective><sentence>Pick up bowl
dump  | the bowl in trash
close the right fridge door  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up bowl
dump the bowl in trash
close the right fridge door</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>20</scenario><objective>7</objective><sentence>Pick up trash bag
pick up coke
put down coke
turn off tv Pick  | up trash bag
pick up coke
put  | down coke
turn off tv  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up trash bag
pick up coke
put down coke
turn off tv</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>17</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Turn on tv
Pick up pillow
Place  | the pillow on the couch
Pick up bag of chips  | and bowl
put down bag of chips and bowl  | on table .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Turn on tv
Pick up pillow
Place the pillow on the couch
Pick up bag of chips and bowl
put down bag of chips and bowl on table</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>13</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>pick  | up pillow
put  | down pillow
pick up chips
put  | chips on table
pick up xbox
put  | down xbox
turn on tv | down xbox
turn on tv .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : pick up pillow
put down pillow
pick up chips
put chips on table
pick up xbox
put down xbox
turn on tv</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>6</scenario><objective>1</objective><sentence>Pick  up ramen
open microwave
start  | microwave .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick  up ramen
open microwave
start microwave</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>7</scenario><objective>3</objective><sentence>Pick up kettle
put  | down kettle on the burner
turn on burner | down kettle on the burner
turn on burner .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up kettle
put down kettle on the burner
turn on burner</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>19</scenario><objective>6</objective><sentence>Pick  | up xbox
put  | down xbox
pick up chips  | and dip
pick  | up pillows
put down pillows on couch
 up pillows
put down pillows on couch
 | up pillows
put down pillows on couch
 .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up xbox
put down xbox
pick up chips and dip
pick up pillows
put down pillows on couch
</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>15</scenario><objective>8</objective><sentence>Pick up the movie
put  | down the movie
pick up chips and bowl of dip
put  | down chips and bowl of dip
pick up pillows
Turn on tv down chips and bowl of dip
pick up pillows
Turn on tv down chips and bowl of dip
pick up pillows
Turn on tv  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the movie
put down the movie
pick up chips and bowl of dip
put down chips and bowl of dip
pick up pillows
Turn on tv</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>16</scenario><objective>9</objective><sentence>Pick up the book
Bring  | me the book
turn off the tv
Bring  | me the chips and bowl | me the chips and bowl .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : Pick up the book
Bring me the book
turn off the tv
Bring me the chips and bowl</span> </sentence></point><point><email>chris.mccloud09@gmail.com</email><scenario>11</scenario><objective>10</objective><sentence>pick up the cd
pick up the chips and dip
 pick up the cd
pick  | up the chips and dip
  | .<br/><span style="color:red">Old text : pick up the cd
pick up the chips and dip
</span> </sentence></point></root>